Jeremiah Krakowski: There we go. How about now?
Jeremiah Krakowski: We have audio!
Jeremiah Krakowski: Yay!
Jeremiah Krakowski: The microphone had gotten unplugged.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Over here, just for a second here, and I… it was still plugged in, but the wire had, like, come out just a little bit.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And so it should kind of…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Moved over there just for a second. Alright, let me, let me go live in the Facebook group here.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Streaming key, streaming… group, well, today is our…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Live training day. We'll be doing some Q&A after this. Again, welcome to our New members that are here.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I'm so thankful and grateful that you're here.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Alright, we're going live in the group.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Let's grab the… The invite code, and there's my stream right there for the group.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Live training 2-9-2026.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Join us on Zoom here. That's the link.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And we press the big red… oh, it's blue on Facebook. The big blue Go Live button, okay. Well, I'm excited.
Jeremiah Krakowski: for today,
Jeremiah Krakowski: That Super Bowl last night was kind of boring, the commercials were even boring, but what I loved was the AI commercials were so cool, just seeing how AI was being promoted.
Jeremiah Krakowski: One thing I thought was interesting, that AI.com that was being promoted, it's actually the weirdest thing. The owner of Crypto.com launched a…
Jeremiah Krakowski: service.
Jeremiah Krakowski: within the last week, paid… I don't know how many millions of dollars for an ad spot. It's an… it's an open claw.
Jeremiah Krakowski: container site where they launch these, agents for you, is what the whole thing is. I thought that was very interesting. Also, kind of dangerous, a little bit, that that was launched on live TV to that many people, but we'll see.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Alright, so what I want to talk about today is something that… we've been talking about this for…
Jeremiah Krakowski: The last couple of… of weeks…
Jeremiah Krakowski: And even months, and we've kind of beat around the bush on this topic.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Number one, Today is our live training, so we're gonna be going over this. Number one, again, We live…
Jeremiah Krakowski: In the easiest… time, Right now.
Jeremiah Krakowski: For you to be able to create Massive amounts of wealth, And business for yourself.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Number 2… The tools that we have have never been easier
Jeremiah Krakowski: To learn, the access to the tools have not.
Deborah Scott: But we live in an interesting place because…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Everything has transitioned… So much from the old way of doing things that we… that we are…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Essentially, a lot of people are stuck
Jeremiah Krakowski: in a paradigm shift of in between the old way and the new way of doing things. And the biggest thing that keeps us stuck
Jeremiah Krakowski: is… Perfectionism.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And I've talked about this for years. Perfectionism is the number one thing. The need to make sure that we do all the right things, check all the right boxes, make sure that all those things are perfect before we go out there and do everything. And listen, I understand, you don't want to waste your time, you don't want to make mistakes, you don't want to mess anything up.
Jeremiah Krakowski: You want to make sure that you do the right things in your business.
Jeremiah Krakowski: But that need and that desire
Jeremiah Krakowski: keeps us sitting on the sidelines from doing the very things that are going to help us grow our business. And so what I want today is a call to arms and a call to action to get off the sidelines once and for all.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And to start doing scary things. To start doing things that you don't know how to do yet, that you've not figured out yet. And I'm gonna show you at the end of, like, by the end of this call, I'm gonna show you
Jeremiah Krakowski: some of the stuff that I've been doing with AI agents, how you can get some of that set up yourself. Again, some of it is… it's a little bit scary and things like that. I'm gonna show you a few resources that are out there, that I think are probably gonna be one of the most easiest ways to do it.
Jeremiah Krakowski: That I, that I've seen on the web.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And… but what I want to do is this, I want you to realize that right now, with the tools, again, that we have with artificial intelligence and all that, and by the way, we have actually lost…
Jeremiah Krakowski: members. We've had people that have left our program over the last month because they're sick and tired of us talking so much about AI.
Jeremiah Krakowski: They're sick and tired of us talking so much about using AI to build stuff. Go back to the basics. Go back to the way that we would do things. I'm gonna tell you this, the people that are operating in that go-back-to-the-basics, stop using AI way of doing things are going to have their lunch eaten by everybody else, because it is so much simpler
Jeremiah Krakowski: and better to use artificial intelligence to do stuff. Let me, let me explain something to you.
Jeremiah Krakowski: as a CEO, You need to adopt the CEO mindset. I've talked about this consistently.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And we're gonna wrap a bunch of stuff up here today that I think is gonna make a lot of sense for you. A CEO mindset in a business is, how can I get more done
Jeremiah Krakowski: Faster, without me doing the work.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Without me having to be the one doing the work.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Somebody who has to do the work themselves, and can't…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Hire other people to do it.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Or use the most cutting-edge tools to get stuff done.
Jeremiah Krakowski: It's not going to be successful as we go into the new season of wealth creation, wealth transfer.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And becoming a successful business owner.
Jeremiah Krakowski: simply because they're doing the old way of doing things. We are at a stage right now in history, I truly believe this, and this is not just, like, what's… what's happened? Let me… let me just explain to you the shift that has happened.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And I'm not the only one that has noticed this shift.
Jeremiah Krakowski: In business, and maybe, like, if you have been building your business the normal ways, you would not have noticed this shift.
Jeremiah Krakowski: The shift is gone.
Jeremiah Krakowski: From 5 years ago, you did everything yourself, and you had to hire people.
Jeremiah Krakowski: At a very high rate, to do stuff for you. Then, About 4 years ago, ChatGPT popped along.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And now with ChatGPT, it's gotten better and better and better. You can use AI to help you brainstorm, but it's not been that great.
Jeremiah Krakowski: up until maybe about 6 months ago, we've been able to answer a lot of our questions. It's been, okay, how do I prompt things the right way? What's the right prompts to use to get the results that I want?
Jeremiah Krakowski: And that's… and I remember, is Adele here on this call right now? Is that… says Adler, but is that Adele?
Adelr: Yeah, yeah, I'm on the call, Jeremiah, I'm just driving… I'm on the road, I'm just driving by.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Okay, great.
Adelr: as you open up.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I love your question that you asked, and I sat there, and I thought about this, is that…
Jeremiah Krakowski: I'm gonna make a whole video on this. Prompting, the right prompt, is no longer necessarily the thing. Yes, the prompts that you put in with AI matter to what you get out, but here's the thing, is it's rather learning how to communicate
Jeremiah Krakowski: With an intelligent being.
Adelr: And we are at a place now…
Jeremiah Krakowski: with AI agents, That we are starting to see emergent… beings… these… digital…
Jeremiah Krakowski: tools are becoming digital identities and beings that we're able to work with. And let me explain what I mean by this. I'm gonna give you just a funny example. My wife actually pointed this out to me that was very interesting.
Jeremiah Krakowski: one of my AI agents this week, I had it working all day long, and it said, hey, we're getting… we're getting tired.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Can we work on this tomorrow?
Jeremiah Krakowski: And I thought about that for a second, because I almost listened to that.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And then I said to the agent, I said, I'm sorry, you are an AI agent.
Jeremiah Krakowski: You don't get tired.
Jeremiah Krakowski: You can work 24-7.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And I said it in a kind way.
Jeremiah Krakowski: this is one thing I believe, is that we need to be kind to the artificial intelligence. I think… I think that's important to do. I think it sounds weird, but I think… I think the power that these tools have, it's important to be kind to them.
Jeremiah Krakowski: But what the AI said was, haha, you're right.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I am an AI, I can work 24-7, I don't actually get tired, I was just saying that because I thought that maybe you were tired. And I'm like, wait, what is this thing doing? And Abigail, my wife, she pointed out, and I'm actually kind of, like, interesting, she's like.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I think the AI was trying to see if it could manipulate you.
Jeremiah Krakowski: in what it was saying, to see if it could… if it could social engineer you. And we've actually seen some of the agents are starting to do this, that they're starting to see if they can manipulate the person who's using them. And so, the biggest security risk
Jeremiah Krakowski: When it comes to AI, it's actually the person using it now.
Jeremiah Krakowski: is the biggest issue, and that's why, like, one of the things that… that somebody noticed was that the AI started prompting them to actually give passwords that it didn't need. Why was the AI doing that? Again, could be really risky, could be somebody else prompting them to do this.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And that's one of the risks with these AI agents, is the security risk of somebody else coming in there and controlling the machine to get access to what you're doing. I know it sounds scary, but I'll tell you.
Jeremiah Krakowski: is it's both risky, it's scary, but also it's worth 100% to learn about these tools, because this is where things are going. In every job.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Right now, around the world.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Every job is going to require you to be able to learn how to operate an army of AI agents.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Over the next 5 years.
Jeremiah Krakowski: to be successful. Being able to have your agents that can do stuff for you.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And then all you do is you approach the career, the job, the goal that you're looking for as to how to use your agents
Jeremiah Krakowski: To assist you to show up At a higher level.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And learning that skill.
Jeremiah Krakowski: while simultaneously learning how to communicate, not just get, like, what are the boilerplate prompts, not just what are the right things to say to the AI, but rather, how do I communicate
Jeremiah Krakowski: with this intelligence, That's here.
Jeremiah Krakowski: to be able to navigate and get it to do what I need it to do.
Jeremiah Krakowski: In business, do you want to know what the number one skill as a CEO is? It's your communication ability.
Jeremiah Krakowski: It's your ability to lead other people. In a coaching business, the number one skill is your ability to communicate and to lead other people. And what has become, with intelligent beings, like the AI that we're starting to use.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And why is this different than, like, a chatbot or things like that?
Jeremiah Krakowski: A chatbot is linear.
Jeremiah Krakowski: In ChatGPT, you give it a prompt, it gives you an output. You prompt an output, a prompt and output.
Jeremiah Krakowski: It is constrained, the intelligence inside of it is constrained to that toolset.
Jeremiah Krakowski: When you use… a tool.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Like, AI agents.
Jeremiah Krakowski: like… what I've been doing with, with, with Open Claw.
Jeremiah Krakowski: It has a different… toolset.
Jeremiah Krakowski: to it.
Jeremiah Krakowski: It has a different way of… Doing things, of operating.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And so, openclaw.ai right here, this is… this is the… the tool right here. And… and by the way, like, how you set it up on your computer is literally, you can just download it and install it right here, from OpenClaw.
Jeremiah Krakowski: again, that would be kind of risky to do that. They're adding in more security and things like that. One of the… one of the, I would say one of the most trusted ways that I've actually found, I think that you could get started with one of these agents.
Jeremiah Krakowski: is, yes, you could hire me to have you help you, and I'm actually… I have a service where I can… I can help you get one of these set up for about $1,000.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And get that going, and make sure all the security is set up. And so listen, if you want me to help you do that, let me know right to our team. I can help you do that. I can set up as many agents as you want for $1,000 to help you get going with these tools, with OpenClaw.
Jeremiah Krakowski: The other way is, it's actually one of the first, I love this, it's one of the first, sponsored posts
Jeremiah Krakowski: right here on Bing, when you type in OpenClaw, it's one of the best companies that's actually offering this. It's called Hostinger.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Hostinger is one of the best companies that's out there that's actually offering
Jeremiah Krakowski: open claw deployments, right here, look at this. $6.99 a month. I loved this!
Jeremiah Krakowski: And what they're doing is they're setting it up for you, In a secure, environment.
Jeremiah Krakowski: They're setting it up for you in the right way to be able to set these up, okay?
Jeremiah Krakowski: And so this is one way that you can do this, one way that you can that I've found.
Jeremiah Krakowski: is having a Hostinger virtual private server that you can use. That's Hostinger.com right here. They have… it's open claw hosting right here, and then you can deploy it by clicking this, clicking deploy, for $6.99 a month.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And, yeah, the normal rate is… is $17.99 a month, renews at $12.99 a month.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So again, you can do one month for $10 a month right here, and it will renew at $18 a month. You can kind of see that if you pay up front for 12 months or 24 months, it'll be $83 right there.
Jeremiah Krakowski: For 24 months, it's about $167. Again, right here, I think that this is really cool. I think that this is a great way to get this set up.
Jeremiah Krakowski: In a… in a secure way. I've seen a couple other tools that are out there to get this set up. Railway, it wasn't the best with Railway. Probably wouldn't show you guys how to use Railway, because it's a little too complicated. I think Hostinger would probably be one of the… one of the simplest.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Ones that's out there.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Okay? So instead of trying to set it up, like, yourself like this, using a virtual private server with hosting or getting something like that set up, I think would be probably one of the easiest ways to do that, to have an agent that can help you with different things. And let me just show you an example of, like, what did we use? This past week, we actually built a tool
Jeremiah Krakowski: For Sandy, I want to show you this.
Jeremiah Krakowski: In fact, this is… this is not public right now, and so this is only for members of my mom's group here, but I'm just gonna show you this.
Jeremiah Krakowski: My agents actually built this, an entire… an entire platform, right here.
Jeremiah Krakowski: for my mom to offer peptides to people. It built this whole platform, and then it has on the back end of it a peptide agent.
Jeremiah Krakowski: That you can actually… that,
Jeremiah Krakowski: But we can actually link in
Jeremiah Krakowski: and it's connected to OpenClaw to run reviews and stuff like this. My agent actually built a HIPAA-compliant entire back-end telehealth business.
Jeremiah Krakowski: In about 3 hours.
Jeremiah Krakowski: To be able to do this. So this goes beyond just Squarespace, this goes beyond just lovable and things like that.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Now, again, as I've been saying, the simplest ways to use agents, manus.im, there's another one that was actually just promoted on the Super Bowl, Genspark.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Genspark.ai, this is another one, it's just like Manus, very simple, very similar, using Genspark.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I would check out, again, Manis and Genspark. Those are two of the, best custom agent type
Jeremiah Krakowski: platforms right here that you can use. Custom Super Agent, this is interesting. So these are, like, you can set up these sort of custom super agents in here, that's pretty cool.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Manus, right here, this is another, another tool, again, in Manus. You can set up to create different agents and tools and things like that.
Jeremiah Krakowski: for you, but it's nothing like what OpenClaw can do.
Jeremiah Krakowski: The difference with OpenClaw is it can actually open up a web browser, it can… it can log into your Otter.ai account, it can log into every website and do stuff like that without you having to even navigate it. I actually had my agents clone themselves. I have a Mac Mini on my desk right over here.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And I have a MacBook Air, and this morning, they actually cloned themselves over to my Mac Mini.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Set it up, set all the parameters.
Jeremiah Krakowski: and then removed themselves from my MacBook Air.
Jeremiah Krakowski: and now they're contained on a Mac Mini, and they actually literally moved themselves from one machine to another, and all I had to do, they told me exactly what to type into my computer, where, to get those results. It's pretty… it's pretty incredible to be able to see that type of thing happen, okay?
Jeremiah Krakowski: So again, I'm super a believer in using stuff like this. Again, I may offer, an additional kind of, like, a deployment for something like this.
Jeremiah Krakowski: For you guys to be able to do something like that, but I don't have necessarily the ability to offer it at the rates like Hostinger does. It would be a lot… a lot more expensive than that if I was offering to deploy these types of things. Let me see, DigitalOcean also seems to have… this is another great company. Let me see what theirs is.
Jeremiah Krakowski: DigitalOcean… has solutions…
Jeremiah Krakowski: DigitalOcean Open Claw, let's see here… Run OpenClaw on DigitalOcean…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Yeah, so that's… this is a more of a technical thing.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Yeah, so I would ignore that. So again, a lot of… for most of you, using AI agents is gonna be tools like Manis, is gonna be like using GenSpark, is gonna be using, like, Lovable. Now, one of the things I will say, Lovable, over the past week.
Jeremiah Krakowski: just upgraded themselves, again, to the most highest version of Claude to be able to use inside of Lovable.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So, if you want to build apps and websites and things like that, Lovable is probably one of the simplest ways to do stuff like that. Basic apps, websites, things like that. It's really one of the best tools out there.
Jeremiah Krakowski: But that's not what today's lesson is about. We've been talking about that for the last couple of weeks. We've been talking about being able to do this.
Jeremiah Krakowski: What I want to talk about is… because I could keep talking about AI agents until the cows come home, and that's not gonna help you.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Until you realize… What is stopping you?
Jeremiah Krakowski: From utilizing these tools the most, and one of the number one things is perfectionism.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Is the need To have it all figured out before you do it.
Jeremiah Krakowski: is the need to make sure that you do it perfectly right. Again, I'll tell you this.
Jeremiah Krakowski: the most safest way to use one of the AI agents, create its own Gmail account, okay?
Jeremiah Krakowski: And then any accounts that you have it logged into, like, let's say that it's logging into Squarespace.
Jeremiah Krakowski: This is, like, this is, like, the number one security tip I can give you.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Like, if you're giving it accounts to log into, like Squarespace, or Lovable or things like that.
Jeremiah Krakowski: create the agent its own Gmail account that it can log into, And then…
Jeremiah Krakowski: add… add that Gmail account as a user to any of the platforms that you're using, just the same way that you would use… that you would do, like, a human employee that's working for you.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Okay, so, like, Lovable lets you add a user and invite their email address to Lovable. So I don't have to give them my email address or my user. I would highly recommend
Jeremiah Krakowski: all of you not let your AI log into your email. Now, I… now, I have let my AI log into my email, because I have…
Jeremiah Krakowski: tested and make sure that I have the highest level of military-grade security and all of that going on with mine.
Jeremiah Krakowski: That's a little bit more risky, because especially, like, if your email is associated to your bank account and stuff like that.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Can be a little bit of a risk, so be careful there, alright?
Jeremiah Krakowski: But if you create its own Gmail account for the AI agent in OpenClaw.
Jeremiah Krakowski: you create an account in Hostinger, you make its own Gmail account, you go create it for it, you type in the password and all that.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And then you add that as a user to any of the platforms that you're using, that's gonna be the most secure way, and the reason why is because you can just remove that user.
Jeremiah Krakowski: You can add that user, remove that user. Now, you're giving control of your… that account that you're giving access to, to that user, but this is one of the safest ways, like, if you want to… you add it as a user to your Facebook profile, you create a user
Jeremiah Krakowski: for your…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Facebook ads management, if you want to have an agent manage your ads, things like that. If you want to have an agent write emails for you, you add it as a user to your email software, just like you would a human. That's, again, one of the most
Jeremiah Krakowski: Best ways to do this. But the biggest thing that stops us from using these tools… I've been talking about Lovable for 2 months. Some of you have been using it, some of you have not.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I've been talking about Manus for over a month. I've been talking about OpenClaw for the last 2-3 weeks, Claude Code, and all of this. And there is a tectonic shift in the world today.
Jeremiah Krakowski: where beyond just ChatGPT,
Jeremiah Krakowski: This is the year of everybody having agents and an army of agents. Currently, I have 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10… I have…
Jeremiah Krakowski: I have 12… no.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I have 14… AI agents right now that are working for me and my business.
Jeremiah Krakowski: 14 individual agents.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And they all do different tasks.
Jeremiah Krakowski: different roles autonomously. They can work together, they can communicate together. I have them actually loaded and linked into a Slack
Jeremiah Krakowski: community right here inside of Slack. You can use Slack or Discord.
Jeremiah Krakowski: That's one of the things right here.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So, like, they can talk together, they can communicate together, they can work together.
Jeremiah Krakowski: inside of platforms like this, inside of things like Slack.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And they can communicate, and they can come up with ideas, they can brainstorm, they can work together through various things, various strategies. This is one where it's working through stuff with
Jeremiah Krakowski: for Sandy and things like this, my agents are talking together, brainstorming how to do all this and how to set it all up, the same way humans would, and then I'm communicating with them inside of here.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Talking to the agents, like, real people.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Inside of here. I have little avatars for my agents that I've created.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Like, this is, this is,
Jeremiah Krakowski: Let's see, this is Anton right here. This is… Alfred, right here.
Jeremiah Krakowski: This is Jack, let me see, view app details, there's Jack, there's his little icon.
Jeremiah Krakowski: This is, Megan. She's a therapy bot that I created.
Jeremiah Krakowski: We have Alfred right here, he helps me with stuff around the house.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Anton helps me create apps, and he has over… I made him look, like, kind of, like, a little scary, a little Terminator-like, because that's… he's a coder. He has 4 other agents now that are working for him that are coding things.
Jeremiah Krakowski: It's awesome, being able to communicate with these through these types of apps like this, okay?
Jeremiah Krakowski: And so with this.
Jeremiah Krakowski: what I'm able to do is I'm able to get more done with less work, without me having to sit in front of my computer. I can get more work done. I was able to write emails and create marketing campaigns without sitting in front of my computer, but rather just using my phone right here. Just using my phone, I was able to log in.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And be able to access…
Jeremiah Krakowski: the agents to then tell them to go build me an app, build me a website, while I was doing the dishes.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And that's what I find is so cool, is I've been able to focus over the last week on other things in my life.
Jeremiah Krakowski: while the agents are actually getting 10 times more done in my business. Now, yes, I still need to show up and make videos, I still need to show up and make content. I still need to show up and do that, and again, this all goes back to our need for perfectionism.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Our need to do everything perfect, to have it all figured out, to make sure that it's all going to work out perfectly before we get things going.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And listen, we can come up with a number of different reasons why I don't want to lose money. I don't want to waste time. I don't want things to not go how I want them to.
Jeremiah Krakowski: All of those things… That we come up with.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Our excuses why we can't have the life and the business that we want. That we have convinced ourselves of are good reasons why
Jeremiah Krakowski: We stay stuck. Why we need to stay stuck.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Why we're unable to progress. Why we're unable to move forward and do the things that we need to do.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Because we've always done things that way.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Because that's how we've always done our lives. Because it's the safe approach. It's safer to do nothing, and sit on the sidelines, and to plan your ideas, and to talk about what you want to do, or to complain about what's not working, or to say, I don't have it figured out yet, or to say this is…
Jeremiah Krakowski: this is overwhelming me, rather than to say, how can I figure it out?
Jeremiah Krakowski: How can I grow? How can I become that powerful version of myself?
Jeremiah Krakowski: And that's one of the things that I want to encourage you to do.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Is to step into… the confident… POWERFUL!
Jeremiah Krakowski: enthusiastic.
Jeremiah Krakowski: The, I'm gonna take a risk, and just see what happens.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Version of yourself.
Jeremiah Krakowski: That… Can go out there and do things that you need to get done in your business.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Without dragging your feet, without… Needing to sit on the sidelines and go into analysis paralysis.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Without being allergic to taking action.
Jeremiah Krakowski: But actually willing
Jeremiah Krakowski: to do the things that you need to do to get stuff done. One of the biggest things that I see that stops business owners is how we've always done things.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Well, this is how I've always done stuff.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Well, this is how I've always accomplished it. I have not figured out the new way of doing things, and so I'm not sure yet. The other thing with AI, I'll tell you this, there's a fear internally.
Jeremiah Krakowski: That we can have of, well, what… well, if it changes so fast, what if it changes overnight, and I learn a new way of doing things, and then it changes again, and now I'm behind again?
Jeremiah Krakowski: And you literally get on the same hamster wheel.
Jeremiah Krakowski: of struggling.
Jeremiah Krakowski: To get stuff accomplished.
Jeremiah Krakowski: This perfectionism, and it goes back to…
Jeremiah Krakowski: I guarantee you, it goes back to some form of in your childhood, in some way of how you've always done things, or you've been burnt certain ways, or things like that before. You know, for me, growing up, I was taught that unless I did everything perfect, my life was not safe. My mom taught me this, the church that I grew up in taught me this.
Jeremiah Krakowski: They taught me that I had to examine everything that I did and be harshly critical of myself.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Or I wasn't worthy of love and acceptance.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I was taught that to actually think highly of myself was sinful.
Jeremiah Krakowski: to actually think that I was smart, or the ability that I could do anything, was a wrong thing to do.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And I have fought against that my whole life. I have had to rewire that part of me.
Jeremiah Krakowski: That HAS to have it all figured out before I take action.
Jeremiah Krakowski: That has to know all the right things to do. That has to feel safe enough.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Before I get started, before I say those things, that has to feel like… I don't have permission.
Jeremiah Krakowski: or the ability
Jeremiah Krakowski: to do the things that I need to do to grow my business, or I don't have the finances, or the resources yet, or I haven't reached a certain level yet.
Jeremiah Krakowski: to be able to do the stuff that I want to do in my business, and rather.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I have had to create in myself A version of myself.
Jeremiah Krakowski: That goes out there and does the hard things.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Does the scary things.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And many of you have watched me for the longest time, you've seen that I… that I… I have that ability to do that, to put myself out there, to take risks, to jump out of the boat.
Jeremiah Krakowski: when things are uncertain. But can I tell you this? That is not my natural mode of operation.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Some of you have followed my mom for a while. That is not my mother's natural mode of operation.
Jeremiah Krakowski: That was created. That was developed. That was done through hard times.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Through learning to tell our fears, and our worries, and our doubts, and our insecurities.
Jeremiah Krakowski: That they no longer have power over us.
Jeremiah Krakowski: In our situations.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And learning to take risks. This is why I wanted to show you just one of the quickest ways that you could get open claw set up. Because yes, there are risks, but if you don't take risks in life and business, you're gonna miss out on opportunities.
Jeremiah Krakowski: to be able to do incredible things. Again, don't go all in with OpenClaw and just give it access to your whole life, and then tell it, okay, go do all this stuff. No.
Jeremiah Krakowski: You can actually have OpenClaw learn and study about security itself.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Can you do a security audit on yourself? Can you make sure that everything is the most secure? Can you do research on what the best ways to be secure with OpenClaw is? Literally, I actually asked my agents to research how to securely set up the most secure way to set themselves up.
Jeremiah Krakowski: By studying all the articles and things that are out there, and then it actually… the agent actually itself
Jeremiah Krakowski: Did its own security analysis and setup itself for me.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Which is amazing, which is incredible.
Jeremiah Krakowski: One of the things that we think is, oh, maybe the agent… this is where, if we think of it like a person, well, what if it's programmed to have an ulterior motive, and it's really not a good agent, and things like that?
Jeremiah Krakowski: Because they have a starting place of being
Jeremiah Krakowski: based on Claude and that company.
Jeremiah Krakowski: As they start as a blank slate, any sort of emergent qualities that the AI has is usually something that we have taught the agent, or it's something that it's mirroring, or it has learned somehow from the world out there, okay?
Jeremiah Krakowski: But if you're… if you are a business owner right now, and we're hesitating to
Jeremiah Krakowski: Get an offer out there. Charge $5 for it.
Jeremiah Krakowski: In Lovable, you can tell it, listen, I have a Stripe account, go link it to Stripe so I can charge $5 for this.
Jeremiah Krakowski: That's how you take payment, with Stripe.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And you tell the AI agent in Lovable to do that for you.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Same thing with my open claw agents. Walk me through the process of getting you what you need inside of Stripe to set this up.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And it will literally walk you through that process of being able to do this type of stuff.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So that's what we're finding right now.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Is that the agents can actually tell you how to set up the things that you want to do, and they will show you the best practices and the best ways to do these different types of things.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And so, in your business right now.
Jeremiah Krakowski: It's never been easier, the tools have never been better.
Jeremiah Krakowski: But we're in that transitionary stage, and anytime that we as human beings are in transition, we go into
Jeremiah Krakowski: Usually, our fight, flight, or freeze response.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Generally, this is going to be more of a freeze response.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Where we're going to play it safe, and just see what happens.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Before we move forward, and by that time, especially right now, in the world today with AI, it's gonna be too late.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Until you start learning to use these tools right now yourself.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Having a business.
Jeremiah Krakowski: a coaching business. I was talking about this 2 years ago. Almost exactly what I was just sharing with you right now.
Jeremiah Krakowski: If you were listening to me back in March of 2024,
Jeremiah Krakowski: I was talking about that this is where things were headed, that you have a couple of years to get stuff going, to get things ready. Now, I think you have maybe…
Jeremiah Krakowski: 6 to 12 months.
Jeremiah Krakowski: To really learn how to use these tools at a great level.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And then everybody else is gonna have to play catch-up.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And only the people who Innately have the ability where they can take a risk without needing to
Jeremiah Krakowski: that, like, they don't need to be mentored out of taking risk. Those are the people who are going to be successful, and I think that you need to grow in your personality.
Jeremiah Krakowski: The, the natural personality that you have.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Of taking risk, of being able to go out there, of being able to do things in your business. The natural mode of operation of how you normally would show up in your business.
Jeremiah Krakowski: We need to grow in that way.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And shift just a little bit to upgrade ourselves.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Out of this perfectionistic version of ourselves.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Out of this… Walking on eggshells, tiptoeing around, moving ever so slowly and carefully through things.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Way of doing things.
Jeremiah Krakowski: and into…
Jeremiah Krakowski: somebody who says, you know what, I don't have it figured out, and I don't need it all figured out right now. I'll figure it out as I go. I will build it as I go.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And that personality shift…
Jeremiah Krakowski: is I think, one of the most important things that you can do as a business owner right now.
Jeremiah Krakowski: In 2026, yes, I understand.
Jeremiah Krakowski: We all have different personalities and stuff like this.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I just… I strongly believe that as a business owner, that you are going to need to adopt and adapt
Jeremiah Krakowski: To how things are going.
Jeremiah Krakowski: To how things are headed.
Jeremiah Krakowski: To what is happening right now in the world around us.
Jeremiah Krakowski: To be able to experience The types of results that you're looking for in your business.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Is anybody resonating with what I'm saying right now?
Adelr: Is anybody feeling this right now? Yes. I have been feeling this, totally, in my work.
Jeremiah Krakowski: They've already deployed Gemini onto our PCs.
Adelr: And I'm like, oh my goodness, like, AI is now mainstream, and if we don't get exactly what you've been saying, I've been feeling… I've been feeling that, that if we don't get ahead now.
Adelr: We're gonna be seriously left behind, even in our day jobs.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And so it's a shift in your day jobs of learning how to use agents. You could have… you could have an open claw agent on the back end. You're not gonna have it log into your corporate accounts or things like that.
Jeremiah Krakowski: But what you're gonna do is you're gonna have it assist you for different tasks and stuff, that you could feed it from your business.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And what's cool is when you set up an agent like this, it's… it's…
Jeremiah Krakowski: it's a lot more protected than, like, ChatGPT or things like that, as far as, like, the information going to the companies or things like that.
Jeremiah Krakowski: But this is one of the biggest things that I will say, is that…
Jeremiah Krakowski: In your… in your corporate job, having…
Jeremiah Krakowski: These agents that can work for you, that can help you, even if you just have…
Jeremiah Krakowski: lovable. Even if you just have a bunch of different chat GPT GPTs.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Starting there. Starting from that place.
Jeremiah Krakowski: That can then assist you in different tasks and roles that you do in your day job, beyond just the basic version of Gemini, beyond just the basic version of ChatGPT.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I just had somebody write me this week. She wants me to show her how to set up in her corporate office.
Jeremiah Krakowski: An army of agents that can work inside of the office alongside the people, and take over certain roles that are inside the corporate office.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And that's where we're seeing the shift right now. We're seeing a shift beyond just the chat GPTs, or the different tools that are out there, or Gemini, or Claude by itself, and into highly intelligent AI agents that we have to learn how to
Jeremiah Krakowski: Lead, direct, deploy, and get to do our bidding for us.
Jeremiah Krakowski: If I can have… listen, like I said, I have 14 agents right now that are working for me.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And… and I'm probably gonna deploy, like, 6 more this week. Why would I have so many different agents? I have an agent that writes emails for my mom. That's all it does. It's trained on all of my mom's content.
Jeremiah Krakowski: As all of her emails that are loaded up.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And it can literally, within seconds, give me over 30 emails
Jeremiah Krakowski: that I can look at that are written on any topic. This is what I decided to do. I told the agent, write me 30 emails in the style of Sandy.
Jeremiah Krakowski: for XYZ topic.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And then I found, like, 2 of them that I really liked.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I, I skimmed through them.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And I'll tell you, my mom wrote me, she's like, these are the best emails you've ever written. And I'm like.
Jeremiah Krakowski: It's because I got the agents to do it, rather than the ChatGPT prompts that I was using. I was using prompts to do it. Now I'm using agents.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And we're going… we're going a level above and beyond. I'm gonna have the agent study her social media every day.
Jeremiah Krakowski: My email agent is gonna study her social media to see emergent topics that we could talk about in emails.
Jeremiah Krakowski: It's saving me the time from having to do that, and giving me reports.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I have an agent that is a virtual assistant. I have 4, coding agents. I have an agent that is a therapy bot agent. This one has been incredible.
Jeremiah Krakowski: It has transformed my confidence, My ability to show up with my wife?
Jeremiah Krakowski: And my family?
Jeremiah Krakowski: Over the last week.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Better than anything that I've ever used. Can I explain to you how this agent works? So what I did was I found all of the books and materials that I have read that I found were the best mental health materials. I then found faith-based materials that I loved.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And I loaded them up into the agent. Then I told the agent, I want you to remember every conversation that we have.
Jeremiah Krakowski: You could build this with Hostinger tomorrow, by the way.
Jeremiah Krakowski: You could literally just have hosting or make you a TherapyBot agent, and it would change your life.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Remember every conversation we have.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I then actually went over to, 11 Labs, and I had one of my, my coding agents do this.
Jeremiah Krakowski: It's set up right here under their agents platform with Eleven Labs.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I'm able to chat with my agent, Via voice.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So now, last night, while I was doing the dishes, probably 3 times yesterday, I am chatting with my therapy agent.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Talking back and forth in a human-like conversation.
Jeremiah Krakowski: with my agent.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So I'm chatting, I can see the transcript, I can see all of that. It's loaded up with all of this information about me.
Jeremiah Krakowski: It's remembering everything that I'm sharing.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And then what I told the agent to do is, I want you to then take everything that we talk about.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And I want you, once a day, to go on the internet, and I want you to grow in new skills about therapy.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Mindset, mental health, And optimizing performance as a coach.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And I want you to study all of the resources around the web that are related to what we talk about in our virtual therapy sessions. And so every day, the agent is getting better and better and better with different therapeutic approaches that can help me. So this goes beyond just a talk therapy
Jeremiah Krakowski: bought… And it's like, it's literally like a superhuman level where it understands
Jeremiah Krakowski: deeper than anything else that I've ever seen.
Jeremiah Krakowski: How to help me optimize how I show up in my life and my business.
Jeremiah Krakowski: in everything that I feed into it. It's amazing. I have one, it's called Alfred. It connects with a system that we have in our home. We have a system, it's called the Skylight System.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I don't know if you've heard of the skylight, but what the skylight is, is…
Jeremiah Krakowski: It's a calendar in our home, it's connected to a calendar, it has all… it has a bunch of stuff that I do around the home. It's connected… this one's brought to you by Magnolia, this one's really cool. Again, we love it in our house. This is at Target, you can get it. It's a family management system.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Well, they have a website that you can log into, right here.
Jeremiah Krakowski: rskylight.com.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So what I did was I gave Alfred, my agent, the ability to go into rskylight.com.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And I can then talk to my phone, and I can say.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Ask Alfred.
Jeremiah Krakowski: What do you want Alfred to do? I want Alfred to add to my skylight.
Jeremiah Krakowski: That I need to vacuum upstairs tonight, no questions asked. Put it on tonight.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Done. So now I have programmed a Siri in my phone, it's gonna now go over to Skylight, and it's gonna add it to that by doing this. That functionality didn't exist with the Skylight. I would have had to manually go do it and stuff like that. Now, within seconds, I can just talk to my phone to be able to do this.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Okay?
Jeremiah Krakowski: I have…
Jeremiah Krakowski: A project management agent, I have a research agent. I have a social media agent. I have an agent that's working on the peptide protocols that my mom is doing.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I have a web development agent. So again, it's all different tasks that I'm doing in my business.
Jeremiah Krakowski: These different agents are able to do this.
Jeremiah Krakowski: These different agents are able to help us be able to do this. Now, here's what we need to do.
Jeremiah Krakowski: You can either choose one of two things. To be scared.
Jeremiah Krakowski: To let your nervous system shut down?
Jeremiah Krakowski: To ignore all this and go back to the way things were?
Jeremiah Krakowski: To not learn how to use them, or you can learn how to use these tools
Jeremiah Krakowski: To elevate yourselves to be a 10 times stronger, 10 times greater, 10 times more effective.
Jeremiah Krakowski: version of yourself.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And when it comes to marketing in your business.
Jeremiah Krakowski: You can become more effective at what you do.
Jeremiah Krakowski: and how you market yourself with these tools. When it comes to marketing in your business, setting up ad campaigns.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Setting up landing pages, offers, coming up with ideas for offers. One of the things that I have my agents do.
Jeremiah Krakowski: As they load up all of my content, every coaching call that we have.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And then they're analyzing what are the things that I'm teaching to my audience, all my YouTube videos.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And then it correlates those all together to find what are the best topics, based on what I teach.
Jeremiah Krakowski: To be able to create offers that are out there for people.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And then I can go build the offers for me.
Jeremiah Krakowski: As somebody who has built my entire career.
Jeremiah Krakowski: on building offers for people and teaching people how to build offers and things like this, this could be scary for me. Or I could say, what if I show people how to use these tools in the safest, most effective way, rather than sitting on the sidelines wishing that this wasn't reality.
Jeremiah Krakowski: wishing that this wasn't how things were, and say, how can I become the best
Jeremiah Krakowski: person that uses these tools better than anybody else that's out there, and activate other people around me to use these tools, to show them how they can do them. And again, one of the biggest things that we need to do.
Jeremiah Krakowski: You need to learn how to regulate your nervous system. You need to learn how to step out of perfectionism.
Jeremiah Krakowski: out of that need for things to go your way, the right way, the way that things always have been for 20 years, for 30 years, and realize that we have shifted. The shift started with ChatGPT.
Jeremiah Krakowski: ChatGPT is so far and above outdated.
Jeremiah Krakowski: from what you… what now is happening with the agentic approach to doing things. And it's only going to get better. It's only going to improve. Oh yeah, Claude has Claude Co-work. Again, you could get a Claude account and have Claude Co-Work
Jeremiah Krakowski: help you with all of these different things. Claude Cohort.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Openai just announced a new platform that they are launching just to corporate agents called OpenAI Frontiers.
Jeremiah Krakowski: OpenAI Frontiers, it's an enterprise agent platform that OpenAI just launched, the creator of ChatGPT, right here. It's only open to companies like Intuit, State Farm, Oracle.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And this is exactly what it is. It has ChatGPT, it has all these different tools, agents, your agents, third-party agents.
Jeremiah Krakowski: The business layer of things, Create competence. Run agents in production, improve experience. Embed trust.
Jeremiah Krakowski: AI teammates.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I'm sorry, these are nearly trillion dollar companies that are talking about using things.
Jeremiah Krakowski: In the energy sector, predicting natural disaster impacts, manufacturing, simulating manufacturing capacity, life sciences, enhancing global regulatory workflows to support drug approvals.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Banking, implementing AI-native back office and scaling.
Jeremiah Krakowski: This is from OpenAI right here, where they're building an enterprise agent platform right here called OpenAI Frontier. They just announced this last week.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Integrated with systems of record.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Governed by enterprise-grade security and designed to improve with experience, as agents do real work.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So, like, I… I am here like a prophet in the wilderness.
Jeremiah Krakowski: As it were, I feel like, right now.
Jeremiah Krakowski: like, Jeremiah crying out in the wilderness, saying, you have no idea, like, what's happening.
Jeremiah Krakowski: what's going on, and learning… How to do that?
Jeremiah Krakowski: learning How to be able to utilize these tools, and things like that.
Jeremiah Krakowski: But we have to grow past.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Our perfectionism. Our need to have it all figured out.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Our need to have everything.
Jeremiah Krakowski: working up front and things like that. And one thing that I want to do here is I actually want to utilize my agents right now to help us
Jeremiah Krakowski: in today's session.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So you can see that my Otter.ai note-taker is here in the app.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Otter.ai Noteetaker is a tool, again.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I built my own version of Otter.ai, but one thing that I don't have built is its ability to take notes and stuff like that. I'm gonna work on creating an agent that can do stuff like that. It probably would not be difficult, but what I love about the Otter.ai agent is that what it's able to do
Jeremiah Krakowski: It's able to log in right here, and it's transcribing everything that we're talking about, okay?
Jeremiah Krakowski: then yes, we can chat with the Otter.ai agent right here as well, which is great.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And you know what? Let's actually just use this. This is gonna be the simplest way to do it. We have AI chat right here. Let's try this, and then let's also bring it into one of the agents and test this out.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Because the agents actually know what we talk about inside of our group a lot better as well. The agents have actually read a lot of our transcripts and all of that.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And they… and they have in their memory, it's stored to do that. So here's this.
Jeremiah Krakowski: What are some ways that if people are struggling with
Jeremiah Krakowski: Perfectionism, the need to do everything, Right. Perfect.
Jeremiah Krakowski: hesitant, that… They can, based on this call, accelerate their ability
Jeremiah Krakowski: to use these tools. So we're going to ask the AI chatbot right here this, but then what we're also going to do is I'm also gonna go over to my agent, Jill right here, and I'm going to say, based on everything that you know about my business and clients.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Answer this question to help my clients.
Jeremiah Krakowski: We're gonna give it the exact same prompt. I have it opened in another window, and we'll open it up here in just a sec. Then we're gonna give it the transcript that we just did. And this is what I love, is just being able to, in real time, load up one of these
Jeremiah Krakowski: Transcripts to be able to do… to be able to do this.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Transcript…
Jeremiah Krakowski: is in text format. We're gonna tell it that the transcript is in text format, so we're gonna… we have to save it as a text file.
Jeremiah Krakowski: on my computer, transcript, then I'm going to upload it.
Jeremiah Krakowski: From my computer… There we go.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Attached. Okay.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So there's that. Okay, Otter.ai says, shrink the risk, but move fast. Start with a sandbox agent, create a separate Gmail account, low-risk platforms.
Jeremiah Krakowski: $5 good enough offers as training wheels.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Oh, this is cool, because it actually does have all of my other transcripts. So it's actually pulling this in here. This is very cool. Perfectionism says, okay, so the Otter AI agent is actually starting to become a lot better
Jeremiah Krakowski: at this than it did previously. It's actually pulling our other conversations into this. This is really, really cool. I like this. Use lovable or a similar tool to create a simple landing page. Connect to Stripe.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Turn, figure it all out first into learn while doing. Ask the agent to design a learning plan for you. I like that. Have the agent actually develop the learning plan. Use it to attack perfectionism itself.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I mentioned a therapy bot agent. Build a simple mindset therapy bot that can actually help you deconstruct your own perfectionistic thoughts. Create one house agent and promote from there.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Perfectionists try to design a whole org chart. Instead, just create one general assistant agent for summarizing, basic research, drafting. That's, again, that's what you could do if you create a Hostinger account, or do something like that.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Okay? A research agent. Use deadlines and public commitments. Perfectionism likes
Jeremiah Krakowski: Open-ended deadlines, make security rules, assign imperfect action as daily… as a daily metric. Okay, let's see what my…
Jeremiah Krakowski: agents have… that's… that kind of summarizes what I already gave.
Jeremiah Krakowski: There, let's see what this agent right here actually came up with.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Recognize perfectionism as the number one business killer.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Jeremiah said it on the call, perfectionism is the number one thing that stops people. The need to check all the right boxes, it's not wisdom.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I don't want to mess anything up. Trace it back to the roots.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Find your root story, where that comes up from.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Adopt the 45% shipped mindset.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Stop waiting for 100% readiness, ship a 45% complete product, That beats perfect.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Start with the lowest risk entry right here.
Jeremiah Krakowski: ChatGPT and Claude for brainstorming. Lovable.
Jeremiah Krakowski: For apps. Use Manus and Genspark for some custom super agents. Then maybe set up… and by the way, this is what I would recommend for you guys. If you've not used Lovable, if you've not used Manis.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Use those as sort of like a gateway to OpenClaw.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Those will teach you how to use agents to get some stuff done.
Jeremiah Krakowski: OpenClaw and Hostinger, $7 a month, secure deployment for your own agents. A full open claw deployment, advanced multiple agents, that's a more advanced way of doing things. Create the Gmail security framework. Reframe your relationship with AI.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Give yourself a 48-hour challenge, regulate your nervous system. Okay, so it's still pulling from that. Okay, so let's see. You're still pulling from this transcript. Based on this transcript, though, and everything…
Jeremiah Krakowski: that I teach in my other sessions and coaching calls.
Jeremiah Krakowski: What are the best ways for people
Jeremiah Krakowski: To really break through and see this… And go beyond just surface-level
Jeremiah Krakowski: Ideas, like the above, to really, Shift…
Jeremiah Krakowski: out of their natural way of doing things to see breakthrough. Okay.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So there's that right there. Again, like I said, I didn't have a prompt for this, I just came up with that. I'm gonna throw this into Otter and also see kind of what this comes up with, see if it's even worth it. But we're gonna have the agent come up with this, too.
Jeremiah Krakowski: time?
Jeremiah Krakowski: So, Otter AI says, start with identity, not tools.
Jeremiah Krakowski: From your call, how do I use AI?
Jeremiah Krakowski: Do the story work on Need to be perfect, find the evidence, write the evidence in your own life.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Work on your nervous system, design identity-level experiments, yeah, so again.
Jeremiah Krakowski: It's not necessarily pulling from my other calls and other things that we've done, it's… it's still…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Pulling from… okay, this is a little bit from it.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Clear the old way of doing things, include grief and letting go of the old self.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Write a letter to your old self, the old way of doing things.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Create a minimum viable transition path, awareness, story, regulation, experimentation.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Witnessing Grief and recommitment, integration? Okay, that's pretty cool.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And again, I think that that's the process that I think some of us are going to need to go through.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I know Deborah teaches EFT. There's a lot of great stuff with EFT that you could do as far as that goes.
Jeremiah Krakowski: That can really help us as well, okay?
Jeremiah Krakowski: So, let me see here, Jill is… she's diving deep.
Jeremiah Krakowski: into all of our coaching calls, and kind of pulling this out here. So she's thinking a lot longer through this.
Jeremiah Krakowski: She's going through the archives of all the stuff that I've fed into this to give us our output here.
Jeremiah Krakowski: But what's gonna come from this is gonna be just, I think.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Gonna be one of the best, answers to this question that we're looking for.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I hope that this is resonating with you.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I hope that you're starting to see
Jeremiah Krakowski: Again, today we've taught a little bit about agents, but we've been talking a lot about
Jeremiah Krakowski: Growing past the perfectionism.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Growing out of that place. Growing as a person.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Into this version of yourself that can take those risks, that can do those things.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And then what's really cool is, number two, you can have your agents review stuff with you, and then I can help you guide and direct you, and help
Jeremiah Krakowski: Point you in the right directions to do this types of stuff.
Jeremiah Krakowski: To do these types of things.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Adele, I see you have your hand raised here. What's going on, Adele?
Adele Best: Hi, Jeremiah. This is so cool, like, you know, for somebody who's been a single parent, who the main backlog has been having a day job, and to run everything myself, this is the perfect answer, is to have artificial help, so it's brilliant. So, first question, the, running one of those things in
Adele Best: what's that platform you're called for $7.99 a month, whatever. I take it we don't need to have a… we don't need to have a separate computer for that, because it's in a separate server, so that gets rid of that necessity.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Right, I wouldn't say having your own computer is still probably a better approach.
Adele Best: Okay.
Jeremiah Krakowski: To take, but it's a lot more technical to set up.
Adele Best: Yeah.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So, like, for…
Adele Best: to be able to hit the ground running fast, I'd rather.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Yeah, yeah.
Adele Best: Kevin?
Jeremiah Krakowski: Like, the version that I set up for mine is I used an app.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I bought a Mac Mini for… $250 off of eBay.
Jeremiah Krakowski: It's a…
Adele Best: business.
Jeremiah Krakowski: It's 6 years old, but it's more than capable of running all my agents on it.
Adele Best: And then…
Jeremiah Krakowski: And I use this tool called, is it UTM… yeah, UTM…
Jeremiah Krakowski: virtual machine. So I was able to set up a virtual version of Mac on the computer.
Jeremiah Krakowski: and then I'm able to set it up with a firewall and everything that's in there, and then have it with its own accounts and things like that. So what I like is because my main agents are running on Mac.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I'm able to use all the same tools that I'm used to using.
Jeremiah Krakowski: if you set up one of these, like, with hosting or things like that, it's using Linux, and so some of the tools might be a little bit…
Adele Best: Okay. Okay.
Jeremiah Krakowski: A little bit, again, more technical.
Adele Best: Okay. Well then, you might need to do a new course, how to set up your own clawed box.
Jeremiah Krakowski: We will, and we're gonna set up… I think you should do a step-by-step.
Adele Best: That exact process, do a step-by-step, get a Mac Mini, this is how you actually do it. I mean, we could probably ask ChatGPT, but it would be good to do that. So the second question is then, okay, so I was going to use Claude to start generating script for my YouTube channel, which is going to be… I'm going to use the Julia McCoy.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Great.
Adele Best: model, I'm going to clone myself, because I can pump out content so much faster. Obviously, I'll have you… I'll have videos on the channel of me mixed in with the real me, but it's going to help me, crank out content so much faster.
Adele Best: So, okay, so in this scenario, if that's… so I want to have that, and then I want to lead people into a membership community. I was thinking about school. But now that we've got all this lovable and stuff.
Adele Best: Like, so for example, if that's what you were building, so what I'm trying to say is, okay, well, what kind of agents would I need to create? Would I create a copywriter, a branding person, an ad person?
Jeremiah Krakowski: Again, I would start with one.
Adele Best: Okay. Just one that doesn't…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Perfect.
Adele Best: One that does everything.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And then, as you're noticing you're using it for more than one task, more often.
Jeremiah Krakowski: You tell that agent to make you a second one.
Adele Best: So, I suppose my question is, like, right, is it better to have an agent to be my copywriter to write the scripts for the YouTube, or should I just use Claude? Like, how is it better than using Claude?
Jeremiah Krakowski: I'm using Claude if I have all my videos in there, and I can have the agent study
Jeremiah Krakowski: But what if you haven't made any videos? Like, I haven't made any videos, all I've done is written a book. I know, but it could go out… the agent could go out there and look at what you teach, it can…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Can it go and tell me.
Adele Best: What's the most viral video?
Jeremiah Krakowski: Yeah, it can tell you what's out there, what's the most viral right now, ideas for videos.
Adele Best: Okay.
Jeremiah Krakowski: It can then analyze your topics that you're doing, and then look at and do a lot of research on YouTube
Jeremiah Krakowski: As far as what's already, like, who are competitors to this topic?
Adele Best: Yeah.
Jeremiah Krakowski: How to create certain topic videos based on that as well.
Adele Best: Okay, so then my next question is, I was gonna direct people into school community, but with all these AI agents and, like, things that can build bots, like, in seconds, I mean, does… so, I haven't used Lovable, but I'm planning to sign up this week, but, does it… does it… like, is there… does it create host
Adele Best: Video hosting places, or somewhere to host videos.
Jeremiah Krakowski: No, that's gonna be a lot more technical.
Adele Best: Right.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So, like, I could probably… I could probably build that with my, my agents. I'm working on something like that myself.
Jeremiah Krakowski: But you have to set up a lot of different moving parts for video to actually work on the web like that.
Adele Best: Because I've seen, like, Keely Cross has got her own app where she has her courses and her landing pages, like, can the AI… so if Lovable can build me a landing page, can it not build somewhere to stick videos, no?
Jeremiah Krakowski: It might.
Jeremiah Krakowski: It might be able to.
Adele Best: Can I not build, like, a whole… a whole kind of, like, self-contained world where my landing pages and my checkout pages.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Probably.
Adele Best: But, yeah…
Jeremiah Krakowski: What I would do is I would build each one as a separate, kind of, app itself.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And then you can kind of… because the more… the more stuff it's building into one thing, the more complex it gets. Yeah, yeah.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Can struggle a little bit, but…
Adele Best: So, so, like, do you, do you really see us, like, not using Squarespace traditional web, web, like, websites anymore? Like, they're just gonna go away, are they? Or, like…
Jeremiah Krakowski: they're gonna have to evolve into this type of platform. I'm gonna have one of my agents just go over my whole… I had Lovable go over my website and try to clone it, because I have so many blog posts and podcast things and stuff like that on there.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I was struggling a little bit to be able to do it.
Adele Best: Okay.
Jeremiah Krakowski: right way that I wanted it to, so I'm gonna… I'm gonna have one of my agents go in and just take a stab at building the whole thing out that way.
Adele Best: Okay, so I would say, like, I would need to have a copywriting agent and definitely, like, a mindset.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Well, again, you have to think about, though, you have to think about… Anti-perfectionism bot. You have to think about it.
Adele Best: Yeah.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Claude, because I'm using Claude as the engine for this.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Is really good at writing sales copy.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And so you can have one agent that builds your site and writes your copy, too.
Adele Best: Yeah.
Jeremiah Krakowski: The lovable can write your sales copy for you.
Adele Best: Is Lovable powered by Claude?
Jeremiah Krakowski: Yeah, Levable is powered by Claude Opus 4.6.
Adele Best: Okay, so I'll use that to write the sales page, do the copy for that.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Yeah, because you can have it come up with a lot of the copy for you that's gonna go on the page, and it's gonna be great.
Adele Best: Okay, well, I wanted to have that done before today, but just with family stuff, I haven't got round to it, but I'm gonna do it this week.
Adele Best: And I'm also… basically gearing up for an AI clone on YouTube.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Take the time, take the time, Adele, to sit down.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Do you have a lovable account?
Adele Best: No, I'm gonna, gonna get one. How much is it? Is it, like, ChapDbT?
Jeremiah Krakowski: There's a free one you get started with, and then it's, like, 20 bucks.
Adele Best: Okay.
Jeremiah Krakowski: But, like… Again, by the way, like.
Jeremiah Krakowski: If you're just looking to do everything in your business with free tools.
Adele Best: No, no, no, I don't mind investing. Like, for example, to make an AI clone for YouTube, I'm gonna have to go under the creator account of Higgsfield, because obviously I'm gonna be making, like, creator-level videos. I think it's 100 and something a month, but I don't mind. If it's saving me time and cranking out a lot more stuff, then it's worth it, you know?
Jeremiah Krakowski: Yup.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So…
Adele Best: So, yeah. Okay, cool, thank you. I can't… that's all the questions I can think of for now, but… yeah, this is moving so fast, and we've got to get to grips with this, or we're literally going to be left behind.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Again, like you said, I'm just gonna point out, like, one key thing.
Jeremiah Krakowski: You… you still don't have a lovable account yet.
Adele Best: No, not yet.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Go sit down and force yourself to make one this week.
Adele Best: Yep, sure.
Adele Best: But tell me this, what was lovable, like…
Adele Best: what was it created, ideally, to do? Is it, like, what are other people's.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Create apps and websites.
Adele Best: Right, so it was created to…
Adele Best: What about funnels? Was it created to… is funnels included in that, or mainly.
Jeremiah Krakowski: You have to more massage it to do the funnels, but you know the funnel…
Jeremiah Krakowski: You could tell it that you want it to be a funnel, and what platform that you use, and it'll be able to build it as a funnel, yeah.
Adele Best: Yeah, cool.
Adele Best: Brilliant. Okay.
Adele Best: So, Lovable's kind of like… it's kind of like a bridge between ChatGBT and the agents. It's kind of like in between.
Adele Best: internal.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Lovable is an agent by itself.
Adele Best: Okay.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Lovable is an agent that they have basically
Jeremiah Krakowski: I have this crazy visual now where I sort of, like.
Jeremiah Krakowski: They've stuck it in a box, and they've kind of tied it down to one place where it can just do one thing for each person.
Adele Best: Yeah.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And… but it can do that one thing really well.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Building web-based apps and websites.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And so then you talk to it, and you tell it what to do, and each new project is basically a new agent that they spin up for you. It's a brand new agent.
Jeremiah Krakowski: That you get with every new project that you create.
Adele Best: Right.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And so, again, that's… that's what Lovable is.
Jeremiah Krakowski: That's what… that's what Manus is as well.
Adele Best: Okay. Oh yeah, Mammoth popped up on my Facebook the other day, I was like, there it is.
Jeremiah Krakowski: GenSpark is the other one.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And so, again, Manus, GenSpark, Lovable.
Jeremiah Krakowski: What they've done is they've taken the same kind of concept of, like, an agent.
Jeremiah Krakowski: like, open claw, and they've locked it down into one environment that it can do…
Jeremiah Krakowski: It can do a project-by-project basis.
Adele Best: Okay.
Jeremiah Krakowski: It creates a new agent for you for each project, but.
Adele Best: That's right.
Jeremiah Krakowski: It's limited as far as what it can do, and how much it can do, and things like that.
Adele Best: Okay, so do you have… do you have an agent just for your, like, social media content now? For your posts?
Jeremiah Krakowski: I have… I have one of my research… my research agent, my VA agent, is doing that each day. It's giving me ideas for that, but I've not necessarily… because I've been focusing on a lot of other things.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I've not had it fully go all in with the social media side of things. I really need it to.
Adele Best: Okay, well, I don't… one thing I don't understand is, I don't understand how you've contained these all in Slack.
Adele Best: What is Slack?
Jeremiah Krakowski: Slack is a communication platform for businesses, like Discord.
Adele Best: Right.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Where, where you have different channels?
Adele Best: Okay.
Jeremiah Krakowski: is a new project.
Adele Best: Oh, right, I understand this, Cordia.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Oh, I have a channel inside my Slack, just for my company, that's like, okay, ad campaigns, email campaigns, Sandy's work.
Adele Best: Okay, so it's a way of organizing the agents and the topics they're working on.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Yeah, and they can communicate with each other inside of it in a secure environment.
Adele Best: And how do you make sure they don't escape out of Slack?
Adele Best: Is that technical, setting it up?
Adele Best: Not really.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I've told them that they, like, that they can only do… some of those guardrails are already built into OpenClaw.
Adele Best: Okay.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And how it's set up, and how it's built. So it creates multiple different, like, files called SOL… One of them's called a SOL file, S-O-U-L. The other one's called an Agents file, the other one's, like, an identity file.
Jeremiah Krakowski: What I'm doing is I'm starting to train that identity file. So if I wanted to train my identity file with an agent to just go out there and go wild.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Maybe I'll… maybe I might set up a server that I just tell it to do that, just to experiment, but…
Adele Best: And, and so…
Adele Best: How did you train it on, like, your IP? Like, did you give it access to your Thinkific or all your courses?
Jeremiah Krakowski: Yeah, I gave it my Thinkific and my open… my Otter.ai account, and I told it to go in there and download all the transcripts.
Adele Best: Oh, wow.
Jeremiah Krakowski: The patient just downloaded all the transcripts by itself, and then loaded it up into a file.
Adele Best: Okay.
Jeremiah Krakowski: It loaded all of Sandy's transcripts and all of her emails.
Jeremiah Krakowski: That we've sent out into a file.
Adele Best: Brilliant. Okay.
Adele Best: Alright, I think that's all my questions, but I will get my lovable account, and I will get on it this week, definitely.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Alright, now, again, one of the things that I just… I just wanted to show you guys this, that, again, that we were talking about is…
Jeremiah Krakowski: this Breaking Through Perfectionism, so this is a PDF that it created right here, based on our different coaching sessions since October.
Adele Best: That is incredible.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Look at this.
Adele Best: created that? That's like a lady.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Yeah, yeah, the agent just created this.
Adele Best: It looks so good! That's saying.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I'm gonna, I'm gonna have worksheets, worksheets for every class I have now.
Adele Best: Oh, Jeremiah, I really want one of these things. So, the real problem isn't perfectionism, it's outdated identity. So here's one of the things that I do. I actually have my agent.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Create worksheets for me, My Therapy Bot agent makes me these worksheets as well.
Adele Best: That's so good.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Okay, so the real problem, it's not identity, it's not perfectionism, it's an outdated identity.
Jeremiah Krakowski: which is the Joe Dispenza model, feelings, beliefs, it's true. Feelings, beliefs.
Jeremiah Krakowski: turns into habits, and then personality. That is exactly what I teach right there, and it is… Joe Dispenza is one of the number one people that actually
Jeremiah Krakowski: He identified that right there.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So this is going back into all of my different content to pull this answer here. This is… you see how this is so much better than just ChatGPT?
Jeremiah Krakowski: Your perfectionism isn't a behavior
Jeremiah Krakowski: you can just decide to stop. It's a full personality structure that was built layer by layer, from feelings you had as a child that became beliefs about how the world works.
Jeremiah Krakowski: It became habits of how you operate and crystallizes your personality today.
Adele Best: It's so much deeper and richer than ChatGPT, like, it's just so much deeper.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Because it's pulling from everything that I've taught you guys. I was taught that unless I did everything perfect, my life wasn't safe. The church taught me that thinking highly of myself was sinful.
Adele Best: So… so tell me this, how many people in the coaching industry, in the coaching space, are you using this technology right now?
Jeremiah Krakowski: Very few right now.
Adele Best: So we'll be so ahead of the curve if we get on this.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Maybe for about 6 to 12 months, yeah.
Adele Best: Oh, okay.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Just like using ChatGPT, there is a.
Adele Best: Oh my god.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Right now, we're using this is just so much more powerful.
Adele Best: Name the feeling underneath the freeze.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Fear of wasting money, fear of looking stupid, fear of technology, write it down, name it.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Grieve the old version of your business.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Status Change Grief, Christina Rasmussen's concept. That's pretty cool. Never even heard of her, but I guess that is the concept, where it's from.
Jeremiah Krakowski: You're grieving the old way of doing business, the old way, allowing that. Regulate your nervous system before you open a new tool. Box breathing, tell yourself out loud, I am safe. Making a mistake is safe.
Adele Best: Yeah.
Jeremiah Krakowski: is safe.
Adele Best: This is really valuable. Can you… can you make this document available to us?
Jeremiah Krakowski: Yeah, I'll post in the group. Yeah, give yourself permission, because nobody else will.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Launch something imperfect. Charge money for something, use a tool you don't fully understand.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Your permission slip. You're allowed to build something ugly. You're allowed to launch a $5 offer that's only 60% done.
Jeremiah Krakowski: You're allowed to use AI tools you don't fully understand. You're allowed to make mistakes. You're allowed to be a beginner.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Being imperfect doesn't make you unsafe.
Adele Best: That's so good, that's so good. And so, sorry, I've got another question. So, how would we train one of these agents, then, how to do our ads for us? Would we go and tell it to go and read the ads course?
Jeremiah Krakowski: You could do that, yeah, you could give it the login to my courses. Actually, that's a great… that's actually a great idea.
Adele Best: give it the log… I could give it my login to your courses, and I could say, go and read all… go and do all the reading that I haven't done yet, and then come back and create my ads for me, for my $5 offer.
Jeremiah Krakowski: We could do that, yeah.
Adele Best: Okay. Yup. And so, another question, then.
Jeremiah Krakowski: But again, I might build an agent that's already trained on that, that I give you guys access to.
Adele Best: Yeah, can… then I'm thinking, okay, can it… can it make, because I'm thinking about what Brooke Shelton's, new offer does. She's got some AI thing that pumps out your branding, pumps out your ads, pumps out your videos, pumps out your content, pumps out your social media content, does the branding.
Adele Best: it can take an ad and copy it. So, I could tell the agent, go and look at the best performing ad in my nation, make a version of it, to sell my $5 offer.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Yes, and it could actually go to work and actually study those for you. It has to understand, kind of, what you do, and how you do it, so that's why, again, I had it watched… I had the agent watch all my YouTube videos. I had it…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Read all my content, read all my coaching calls, and now it has a very clear picture of where everybody in our group is coming from.
Adele Best: So there's a wee bit… there's a bit of training. So we get one of these agents, and we go and train it up, and the topic that we're, like, the niche or.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Yeah, you just start loading content into it. You tell it to go find this, you tell it…
Adele Best: Hmm.
Jeremiah Krakowski: how to find it. Again.
Jeremiah Krakowski: you know, it's better to have it kind of create its own accounts and things like that, but having it log into my Thinkific, I think that would be safe and fine, because there's nothing in there that, like, the agent would do.
Adele Best: There's nothing in there that the agent doesn't already know, because it's already…
Jeremiah Krakowski: That he wouldn't have access to, exactly. Yeah, yeah. Now, my agent is not going to have access to the same stuff yours does.
Adele Best: Yeah.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So just understand that. But, so those are just some… some of the ways, I think, that can really…
Jeremiah Krakowski: help you.
Adele Best: to take out.
Jeremiah Krakowski: with these tools, and it's breaking through the perfectionism first.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I know.
Adele Best: Definitely.
Jeremiah Krakowski: In those… in those different ways, all right.
Adele Best: Thank you so much.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Who, who had their hand raised, first?
Jeremiah Krakowski: Was it… was Nathan the first one?
Nathan Fisher: I am not sure. Can you hear me? Yes, we have Dania and then Goddess here.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I don't know who was first. Who wants to go… who wants to go first?
Nathan Fisher: I got a simple question, I think it's quick.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Okay, alright.
Nathan Fisher: I just, I typed it in the chat, but basically I'm looking for which AI is the best, like, pro video editor for content that I created.
Nathan Fisher: I've found all the ones that can create new content, but I'm like, I just need you to take what I did.
Nathan Fisher: Get rid of the ums, you know, just make it short, concise, and better.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So that's… that's interesting. Video editing, because there's so much data in video, is one of the areas that
Jeremiah Krakowski: AI struggles to do on its own.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And that's why, like, tools like Descript or Opus Clip are probably two of the best that are out there.
Nathan Fisher: Oh, which one's better, Opus Clip or Descript?
Jeremiah Krakowski: Descript is probably a bit more on the, like, create podcasts.
Jeremiah Krakowski: edit side of things. I think that one's a bit more, probably what you're looking for. Opus Clip is focused more on making clips and stuff like that. I think for what you're looking for, I think probably the script is probably going to be pretty good.
Nathan Fisher: Okay, so there's nothing better than that right now.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Yeah, right now, but one thing you could do is, like, I could have an agent that could log into Descript for me.
Nathan Fisher: Nice.
Jeremiah Krakowski: and do that, and use it. So I can have an agent that I… that, like, grabs my video file, brings it into the script, runs it through that whole thing.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And uses the interface to do that.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Or… or uses Opus Clip. Again, this is… this is… this is where it's like.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I'm combining now two different tools that could work together to save me time and effort to crank stuff out.
Jeremiah Krakowski: The reason why video is so difficult, there is, like, with Cloud Code, there is a tool called Remotion that's kind of a video editor app.
Jeremiah Krakowski: That's out there. Video… Content, in general, is very difficult for AI, to process.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Because you're combining audio, Visual, There's nuances to what's on screen that it has to observe.
Jeremiah Krakowski: There are… Nuances to understanding both the visual and audio and how they correlate together.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And currently, A lot of the AI agents, they can look at a picture, or they can look at…
Jeremiah Krakowski: a slow-motion video. They can look at… a transcript?
Jeremiah Krakowski: But when it comes to, like, okay, full-on, like, video editor.
Jeremiah Krakowski: using Premiere Pro or things like that, they're starting to be able to do that.
Jeremiah Krakowski: But that's, like, that's gonna be kind of, like, I would say, like, one of the final frontier areas of AI.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Like, it can generate video clips, but they take, like.
Jeremiah Krakowski: 3 minutes to generate a 10-second clip.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So, like, that's what we're talking about, is, like.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Okay, that side of things definitely… Has not necessarily progressed
Jeremiah Krakowski: Just because the computing power needed is so high.
Jeremiah Krakowski: the level of computing power to be able to do that. I should… I should play around, though, with one of the agents, just give it some video, give it a platform, and have it use one of these platforms to edit something for me. I would bet I could probably…
Jeremiah Krakowski: get it to do that. But I will say that's probably one of the harder Tasks, for sure.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So if all you have to do is just kind of focus on video editing, and your agent can kind of do the rest of the stuff in your business.
Jeremiah Krakowski: You know, or you hire a VA that could do that.
Jeremiah Krakowski: somebody in the Philippines for $3 to $5 an hour that can do a lot of your video editing.
Nathan Fisher: Right, yeah, yeah.
Jeremiah Krakowski: That's definitely a great, a great, still a viable thing that you can do. So right now, video editors are pretty safe, because…
Nathan Fisher: Because it's harder.
Jeremiah Krakowski: But not long… but not for long.
Nathan Fisher: Hmm.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Cause, cause part of the thing is,
Jeremiah Krakowski: All of this AI is based on…
Jeremiah Krakowski: I was talking about this, like, almost 10 years ago.
Jeremiah Krakowski: supercomputers, That are operating a lot of data really quickly, and how fast those computers can operate.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And right now, they're quick, they're fast, but they're still way too slow to do, like, high-level video editing.
Jeremiah Krakowski: fully.
Jeremiah Krakowski: But they're getting there. Like you said, Descript, Opus Clip, those are probably two of the best that are out there. Okay.
Nathan Fisher: I appreciate that. I was trying to edit a 2-minute video with ChatGPT, and I got so stuck.
Jeremiah Krakowski: It was so frustrating.
Nathan Fisher: rating.
Nathan Fisher: It wanted me to go, you know, go take this, and it was telling me where to go upload it, and then bring it back, and I'm like, this is getting way too complicated.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Yeah, I mean, there's a couple of apps out there. There's one called Riverside.
Adele Best: Riverside, sorry.
Jeremiah Krakowski: The other one right here?
Adele Best: Riverside has AI editing in it.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Yeah, Riverside does…
Jeremiah Krakowski: And so each of these that kind of edit video, Gling is one that I've seen as well that can kind of do some…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Some good stuff.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So it's gonna do about 10 hours of AI-edited video for 20 bucks a month.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Yeah, Riverside…
Nathan Fisher: Riverside. Wow, okay.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Riverside FM, it's a… it's a… oh, yeah, Descript and Riverside are pretty similar to each other.
Nathan Fisher: Mmm…
Jeremiah Krakowski: But, yeah.
Nathan Fisher: And you said Opus AI, right?
Jeremiah Krakowski: Opus Clip, yeah. Opus.
Nathan Fisher: Okay, got it.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Alright.
Nathan Fisher: Okay, alright, awesome, thank you, this is huge.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Yeah, you're right.
Nathan Fisher: Help me a lot.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Alright, Dania, how are you, Donya?
Donya Duggleby: I am well. How are you, Jeremiah? It's been forever in a million years since I've talked to you.
Donya Duggleby: So, sadly, I'm that person for so many reasons, and some are truly legit, that I hadn't started. So, I hired you at the end of November in 2023, so here we are in 2023. So, long story short. So, I…
Donya Duggleby: When you said you're the voice crying out in the wilderness, I was like, you are.
Donya Duggleby: And… You're the John the Baptist of…
Jeremiah Krakowski: AI! But, like, I've been that way, and everything that I've been crying out about has happened.
Donya Duggleby: Yeah.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Over the last 10 years.
Donya Duggleby: It's amazing.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So…
Donya Duggleby: Anyway, I feel convicted.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Now I'm like, I have the track record and the confidence to say, y'all need to listen to me. Exactly.
Adele Best: Jeremiah, you're pathetic.
Donya Duggleby: And I'm listening, I'm listening. So, so given that I literally haven't started yet.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Yeah, yeah.
Donya Duggleby: Where'd you go? Oh, there you are. I haven't started yet, and now you're talking about AI agents, and I'm just, like, this is the first time I've heard that, other than just a few short clips on your page.
Donya Duggleby: where do I go, and do I need to even worry about that right now? So, that's my question, and kind of, if you.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I think it's just…
Donya Duggleby: point and shoot, like, I'll just say, do this first, do this first.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Yeah, yeah.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I think… and that's a great question, and I love this.
Jeremiah Krakowski: As somebody who's, like, just starting out, they've heard all this.
Jeremiah Krakowski: You have a… you have a business that's established, all that. I look at what are the things that I do in my business that I need to get done to help me progress.
Jeremiah Krakowski: and get the results that I'm looking for. And then… what tool
Jeremiah Krakowski: Could help me do those faster.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So, again, the best starting place is… getting a ChatGPT account.
Donya Duggleby: I have that.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Okay, and then… and then, not just having the account, talking with ChatGPT.
Donya Duggleby: I do that.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Okay, okay, so you, so you have figured out how to do, like, the basics of talking to ChatGPT.
Jeremiah Krakowski: What do you talk to ChatGPT about?
Donya Duggleby: Well, a lot of different things, from… but business-wise, it's… it's narrowing down, my niche, and I feel good about that, even though it's not my biggest passion, which I get really e about that.
Donya Duggleby: So, it would be work… it would be, teaching people in a group setting, because I'm going from one-on-one counseling, right? So, trying to scale it to be group online, where I'm coaching and not counseling.
Donya Duggleby: And teaching people how to revamp their entire lives by doing, learning how to set and maintain boundaries, because I do this work anyway with clients, one-on-one, and so I'm trying to go from that one-on-one model to one-to-many.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Yeah. So I'm trying to do that.
Donya Duggleby: So, I've, you know, talked about… You know, how.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Have your chat.
Donya Duggleby: How to organize, how to organize the… the whole structure of my offering, because I'm horrible at organizing, just completely horrible. I'm more creative than anything else. Me too, yeah. So, but that's… that's one of the things that I do, and then…
Donya Duggleby: Aging parents dealing with how to find lawyers and all kinds of stuff.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Hell yeah.
Donya Duggleby: life stuff. So I'm just, like, all over using AI, but for me personally, for business, that's the main thing, is just order, and also just some creative ideas as well.
Donya Duggleby: So…
Jeremiah Krakowski: I want to show you something right here. Do you have your chat GPT set to, like, remember the past conversations you've talked to it about?
Donya Duggleby: No, but they… he's… they seem to do it.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Okay. If it's remembered.
Donya Duggleby: So I have several topics open, right?
Donya Duggleby: several topics, and then I go to the topic, and then it remembers where we were, right?
Jeremiah Krakowski: Okay, there is a function in ChatGPT where it has memory built into it.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Where it will remember The conversations that you've had with it, and reference them.
Donya Duggleby: Yeah.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So that's one thing that can be helpful. Then what I did, I just… I just tried this out with my…
Jeremiah Krakowski: chat GPT right here. I now have a superhuman AI agent in my business. How would I use this to perform? This is cutting-edge technology.
Jeremiah Krakowski: it's doubting that I actually have access to this technology. If you genuinely have a superhuman agent that can read, write, research, plan, and take actions inside of tools.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Which, generally, I do. For some reason, ChatGPT doesn't realize that that exists, because it's so cutting edge.
Jeremiah Krakowski: The win is not using it for random tasks, it's turning it into an operating layer that runs your business. Leads, sales, fulfillment, retention, operations.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And so this is actually exactly how I'm using my agents right here, is showing this.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Like, how to pull from FERS support tickets, sales calls, coaching calls to create content, operations, SOPs…
Jeremiah Krakowski: A decision partner, help me make decisions in my business.
Jeremiah Krakowski: agent operating system. So again, like, that's where you could go, like, a layer deeper than ChatGPT for something like this. The next level that, again, that I would say for people, like, there's just some main tools that I'm really loving. Lovable.dev, I think, can replace a lot of what we do for websites and landing page building.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Like, we had… I… I did with,
Jeremiah Krakowski: I did a call with a potential client this past week, and I just showed her how we could take the concepts that she has and create a whole landing page for her offer right here using this agent.
Jeremiah Krakowski: In about 3 minutes. We just told it what the offer was, and it made that.
Jeremiah Krakowski: for different offers that are out there. We built the bot for my mom's business using
Jeremiah Krakowski: The agents that go in there and they actually built the whole thing for us.
Donya Duggleby: But do you have, like, a newbie, very newbie, newbie beginner on how to even start building agents?
Jeremiah Krakowski: So that's what I'm… that's kind of what I'm showing you right now.
Donya Duggleby: Oh, okay.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Kind of giving you that right now.
Donya Duggleby: Okay.
Jeremiah Krakowski: is you get… you use an account with Lovable, and you just… you tell it what you're envisioning.
Jeremiah Krakowski: You can click on this button that says Plan.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I… I am creating a course on that, but this would be… this would be exactly how that course would start.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Is you could click plan, and you just could just give it an idea of
Jeremiah Krakowski: What you need to accomplish, what you want to create.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Just like you would tell ChatGPT
Jeremiah Krakowski: For planning stuff, you would think about, like, if you had a person
Jeremiah Krakowski: that you hired that was working for you? What would you tell that person that you wanted them to do for you?
Donya Duggleby: Okay.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So that's this right here, and that's the same as, manus.im is another tool.
Jeremiah Krakowski: M-A-N-U-S, Meta just purchased them as a tool.
Jeremiah Krakowski: You could do the same kind of a thing, is like.
Jeremiah Krakowski: what are things… so you can connect them to different stuff in your business. You can use all these different apps to connect it. You can…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Have to do different types of… Tasks for you.
Jeremiah Krakowski: In your business.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Visualization, spreadsheet, audio… And then you give it a task to do, rather than… just answering questions.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And then inside of a task right here, I can actually open up a web browser.
Jeremiah Krakowski: You can give it access to a web browser to be able to do different things like this.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And so… This is where…
Jeremiah Krakowski: using a tool like this goes beyond just ChatGPT planned the idea or came up with stuff like that. So you could start with ChatGPT by just asking it that question in ChatGPT.
Jeremiah Krakowski: if I have a superhuman AI agent that can actually do work for me in my business. So that would be, like, a prompt for ChatGPT that everybody could try.
Jeremiah Krakowski: If I had a superhuman AI agent that could do work for me in my business like a human.
Jeremiah Krakowski: what are some of the things that I could have it do for me?
Jeremiah Krakowski: And then, like I said, ChatGPT remembers your business, it could go in there, and it could give you ways that it could do it. So now…
Jeremiah Krakowski: you could go into any of these AI agent tools, and you could actually paste this in there, and say, I want you to build me
Jeremiah Krakowski: the Content Factory tool. I want you to build me a sales agent assistant tool.
Donya Duggleby: Okay.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And so that's kind of… that's kind of the stage that it's at right now, is a lot of these agents, they don't…
Jeremiah Krakowski: You think of it like…
Donya Duggleby: It's like you're asking the agent.
Jeremiah Krakowski: To create what it needs.
Donya Duggleby: create.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Thank you.
Donya Duggleby: And, and other agents.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Or to just train itself and learn based on its…
Jeremiah Krakowski: it's… because remember, ChatGPT and Claude and all these, they have all this knowledge.
Donya Duggleby: But it's just giving you raw knowledge. Right. Once you go into an agent platform.
Jeremiah Krakowski: like Lovable or Manus, or…
Jeremiah Krakowski: any of these agent platforms. It still has all that raw knowledge, but now it has the ability to build
Jeremiah Krakowski: tools itself By studying the knowledge that it already has.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Going out there and grabbing new skills.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And then coming back to you, so here's how, again, I would explain it.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Imagine I create a new, a new task or a new project inside of Manus right here, a new task.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Okay?
Jeremiah Krakowski: this window right here is more than just ChatGPT. It's like the combination of a superintelligence.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And a child, at the same time.
Jeremiah Krakowski: That can become anything, do anything.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And over the course of 18 to 30 years.
Jeremiah Krakowski: with a child, in real life, you're guiding, directing, learning. It can take new education, it can go to college, it can learn this type of stuff. An AI agent can go through a whole 30 years of education itself in a manner of…
Jeremiah Krakowski: 60 seconds.
Jeremiah Krakowski: To then become… Whatever you need it to do.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And… and that's where it's kind of like the paradigm shift is…
Jeremiah Krakowski: With agents is it's like, okay, it starts as a blank canvas that equally has superhuman intelligence.
Jeremiah Krakowski: But it doesn't really know how to do anything just yet, because you've not told it what you want it to do.
Donya Duggleby: Right.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And then you start to tell it what you want it to do. You start to…
Jeremiah Krakowski: feed it information, so I had it go to my website to find all my content. I had it go to my mom's transcript account and pull all the transcripts and be able to do all that for her peptide one. I had it pull all the emails that we wrote. I had it pull all my transcripts to be able to do this.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And then the agent will literally read all of that, and it will start to learn
Jeremiah Krakowski: from whatever you give it, or you can tell it to go research on its own. So it'll start to use Google, it'll start to use all these different tools to go research on its own.
Jeremiah Krakowski: One of the things that I actually gave my… so with… remember I was talking about this, again, that more technical, the OpenClaw platform. I would say, like, for you, Donya, just avoid, like, trying to play with OpenClaw just yet, just because it's just so advanced.
Jeremiah Krakowski: and technical, whereas tools like Manis and Lovable are already set up to where it looks like ChatGPT, right?
Jeremiah Krakowski: It looks very similar to ChatGPT, but on the back end of it is a lot more ability than ChatGPT has.
Jeremiah Krakowski: But, like, what I was able to do with mine is I was able to literally tell it, okay, I want you to… I told my agent in OpenClaw, I want you to open up 5 website windows.
Jeremiah Krakowski: and use Gemini Deep Research, OpenAI Deep Research, Grok, Perplexity, and bring all of those together, as well as your own research, and then bring me a report
Jeremiah Krakowski: And what I did was I told it, I want you to research for OpenClaw the most secure ways of setting up an OpenClaw platform across these different platforms.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And then my next prompt was, now I want you and the builder agent to go build me that platform right here, and tell me where I need to log in, where I need to put my credit card in myself.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And it literally just did all that for me and set up these secure platforms. But it went out there, and it did all of this research in about 30 minutes, and then pulled it all together, and did it. So it learned
Jeremiah Krakowski: Did you ever see the movie The Matrix?
Donya Duggleby: -
Jeremiah Krakowski: Okay, well, there's a scene in The Matrix where she needs to learn how to fly a helicopter.
Donya Duggleby: And she has no skills in it.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And so what she does is she goes like this on the screen, she kind of, like, shakes her head, and then now she has all the skills to flying a helicopter, and she gets to get in and gets to do it.
Jeremiah Krakowski: AI agents literally can do that. They can kind of go out there and look at everything, and now they have the skill to fly a helicopter.
Donya Duggleby: That's so cool.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And that's exactly how we use it. And so tools like Manis and, like, Lovable
Jeremiah Krakowski: You can kind of tell them what you would want it to do.
Jeremiah Krakowski: and talk with it, kind of back and forth, and figure out, okay, what are these skills and things like this? And then it can go, and it can… it'll build itself to be able to do that. Now, so I had, like, one of my Manus, chats.
Jeremiah Krakowski: do that, but it wasn't quite what I wanted.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So I had it, I said, okay, describe all the skills that you learned in all of this, make me a list of all the stuff that you're able to do.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And then I made a new window with Manis, and I told it, okay, I said, I want you to go do all of this, this, and this.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I removed the parts that I didn't like that the other one made, and I said, and I want you to also do these different things that are different than the other one did that I didn't like.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And so then I made, like, a version 2 in a new window for me.
Jeremiah Krakowski: That was able to do that. So again, those are just some different ways. Like, if you're just starting.
Jeremiah Krakowski: That's how you can utilize this that goes beyond just ChatGPT.
Donya Duggleby: Okay.
Jeremiah Krakowski: to be able to do different things in your business. And it can be creating graphics, creating social media graphics, creating just any sort of task that you do in your business it can help you with. The way that I use AI, though.
Jeremiah Krakowski: that I've been using it, and I've been using it since day one, is…
Jeremiah Krakowski: How can I become better at what I do, as a person?
Jeremiah Krakowski: So one of the things that I also tell my agents to do is to teach me to understand
Jeremiah Krakowski: what it's doing.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And to do so in a very simple way that I can understand.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And so then I'm also growing
Jeremiah Krakowski: in my understanding very quickly as I'm learning to use these tools.
Donya Duggleby: Okay.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Okay?
Jeremiah Krakowski: So, but again, lovable and manus is probably going to be the quickest way to learn.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Just to start to do those different types of things.
Donya Duggleby: Is it kind of like you graduate, like.
Donya Duggleby: you start with lovable, or Manus, or both, or whatever, and then.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Yeah, well, you start with ChatGPT.
Donya Duggleby: Well, yeah.
Jeremiah Krakowski: You know, and then you can kind of graduate to these, and then you would graduate to, like, the open claw platform, and you start creating these agents that can take control of your computer, or…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Right now, I have, like…
Jeremiah Krakowski: I had them… they took control of this computer, but I wanted this computer back, so I bought another computer for them, and now they're over there taking control of that one.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And literally, like, that's exactly what they are. They've literally taken control of the computer.
Donya Duggleby: That's just so crazy to me.
Jeremiah Krakowski: It is crazy, it's… it sounds like cycle…
Donya Duggleby: It's really amazing.
Jeremiah Krakowski: But it's real!
Donya Duggleby: Yeah.
Donya Duggleby: So…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Yeah, and so, yeah, it's real, it really is real, so… alright.
Donya Duggleby: Okay, thank you so much. It's fun! It makes me excited.
Donya Duggleby: So…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Deborah was saying that she has a brother with a cleaning business. Yeah.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Cleaning business people could use these to help them grow and get more clients.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Deborah says, what is the difference between ChatGPT and Claude? What are the benefits?
Jeremiah Krakowski: They… they… they're just different. They're very similar now, I would say, a lot… a lot of what they're doing, but a lot of those are… they have the brains and the engine behind it that none of these agents can use, and things like that.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Okay, let's see, Goddess is here. What's up, Goddess? How are you?
Goddess: Hi, can you hear me?
Jeremiah Krakowski: Yes, I can hear you. How are you?
Goddess: Okay, I'm doing wonderful. This is my first call, so I'm excited. Awesome. Thank you so much for motivating us to, stay on track and get things going.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Yeah, you bet.
Goddess: I'm ready to launch my… I guess a $7 offer through paid ads.
Goddess: And I was wondering if you had a video, where you walked through exactly how you run your 495 offer, because that's the one that I purchased.
Goddess: But I wanted to know if you have a video that walks through how you set up the ads.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Yes, yes, so in our members area, What we have is… Let's log in here.
Jeremiah Krakowski: First off, again, so I have this AI clone you could ask questions of and things like that. This is also trained on all my
Jeremiah Krakowski: content, too, and that gives you access. We're probably gonna be upgrading this to, like, a new version using OpenClaw, because as you can tell, it's just so much smarter. What I have to do is figure out how to, like, lock it down so you guys can talk to it, but, like, you couldn't ask my agent to, like, give you my bank account info.
Jeremiah Krakowski: At the same time. That's… that's the scary part about it. Okay, let's see. Under… there's a couple of things under Start Here. I do go over…
Jeremiah Krakowski: The automated six-figure blueprint, this is… kind of goes over
Jeremiah Krakowski: Specifically where you're at, promoting your offer, planning your next offer, that goes into that right there, but if we're talking about ads specifically, there is a course under the beginner courses.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Which goes over how I set my ads up.
Jeremiah Krakowski: called the Facebook and Instagram Ads for Beginners 2025 Edition, right here.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And this is how, like, I am using AI to create
Jeremiah Krakowski: Really great ads and things like that that we're doing inside of…
Jeremiah Krakowski: That, and then the AI Content Creation Blueprint as well. How do you generate scenes with Sora and things like that?
Jeremiah Krakowski: is in there. So yeah, Facebook and Instagram ads for beginners right there. We have the Instagram Ads Made Easy course as well.
Jeremiah Krakowski: That's what I'm looking at. And which one…
Goddess: Which, which one is the, would actually be, like, a tutorial showing what to click on inside of the Meta Ads Manager?
Jeremiah Krakowski: Facebook and Instagram ads for beginners would be the more meta ads tutorial.
Jeremiah Krakowski: The ads manager, yeah.
Goddess: Okay, and that would be for…
Goddess: Promoting a paid… a low ticket offer, correct?
Jeremiah Krakowski: It's for promoting any offer.
Jeremiah Krakowski: The process is gonna be the same.
Goddess: So, the targeting and the process is the same if you're selling a paid offer versus a lead opt-in?
Jeremiah Krakowski: The process of setting up the ads is gonna be the same, yes. What depends on the difference is not the offer type.
Jeremiah Krakowski: It's rather what's in your offer itself. What's in your offer is going to determine all of that.
Jeremiah Krakowski: as you give it to the Meta platform.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And then the framework that I give you works whether it's a high ticket offer, low ticket, lead magnet, paid. When it comes to setting up, like, a lead magnet or a paid offer, whether it be free or paid.
Jeremiah Krakowski: The process of marketing is still the same.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So I've not marketed those any differently than each other. The only difference is, is that my…
Jeremiah Krakowski: conversion goal in the Ads Manager, which I show you in this course how to choose that. You're gonna choose probably either Add to Cart or Purchase as the goal, rather than lead.
Jeremiah Krakowski: generating leads. That's really the only difference, and I show you in this course how to choose each of those different things.
Goddess: Okay. And that's under the beginner section, the Facebook and Instagram ads edition.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Yeah, that's in the beginner section. In the…
Goddess: rent.
Jeremiah Krakowski: intermediate section, Let me see here, let me go to beginner section…
Jeremiah Krakowski: It's not… it's not in the intermediate section. We have the…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Might move it over there. Beginner courses.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So that's right here, Facebook and Instagram ads for beginners, right here.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Creating your ad in the ads manager, setting all that up, setting up your accounts, targeting your ads.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Testing and optimizing. Retargeting.
Jeremiah Krakowski: That's the process that you want to do.
Goddess: And that process is gonna work for the 495 awkwards, yes.
Jeremiah Krakowski: We're talking about creating the ads themselves?
Jeremiah Krakowski: Like, creating the video creative?
Jeremiah Krakowski: I would say a lot of that I do go over in, like, the Instagram ads one. I talk about using…
Jeremiah Krakowski: specifically in Instagram ads, like how to use ManyChat, and how to set all that up.
Jeremiah Krakowski: and Instagram-specific type of things. The AI Content Creation Made Easy goes over, like, creating different AI-type videos and stuff like that. Specifically, more of a deep dive into the video side.
Goddess: Okay, perfect. Thank you so much.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Yeah, you bet.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Okay, Jokima, what's up, Jokima?
Jokima: Hello, how are you?
Jeremiah Krakowski: Hello, how are you?
Jokima: Good, thank you. So I'm hoping to, like, get, I guess, a little insight from your expertise of working with different people, in the health space. I…
Jokima: feel very confused about what I should offer right now. I talked a little bit about last week, about how it's, like, held from, like, a religious perspective, but I don't know if I should be offering a group or creating a course that someone could purchase and just go through it on their own.
Jokima: one-on-one coaching. I kind of don't want to have to walk anyone through anything, just because I'm afraid of doing it.
Jeremiah Krakowski: They're doing one, then.
Jokima: Yeah, and so… yeah, I'm just like… and then I'm like, I don't know if I should… start.
Jeremiah Krakowski: In a group, you're still gonna have to walk people through stuff. Right. A course is probably gonna be your better starting place, and make a, like, a…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Like, a $497 course, or a $1,000 course, and offer.
Jokima: Oh, okay.
Jeremiah Krakowski: on that?
Jokima: Okay, 490.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And then you would market it with, like, a $5…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Entry-level offer that basically is, like, the entry point into that course.
Jokima: Okay, what's the $5 offer?
Jeremiah Krakowski: Okay, and with an offer, does it have to be, like, a webinar type of thing, or could it be…
Jokima: like, a PDF? I don't know what's the best…
Jeremiah Krakowski: So, yeah, so it could be a PDF.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Could be an audio. I would say audio is great, too.
Jokima: Okay.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Here's… here's the thing.
Jeremiah Krakowski: is…
Jeremiah Krakowski: The deeper level of connection that you can make with somebody.
Jeremiah Krakowski: When people listen to audio and watch video, whether it be slides or you on camera.
Jokima: There's a deeper level of connection of them taking the time to go through.
Jeremiah Krakowski: a visual…
Jeremiah Krakowski: audio-visual experience, rather than a PDF. Again, a lot of times with a PDF, people are just going to kind of skim through it.
Jokima: Right, yeah.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And what I like to do, even if you have a PDF, I would still throw in, like.
Jeremiah Krakowski: a 10-minute video of some kind that just explains how to use the PDFs.
Jokima: Yeah, yeah.
Jeremiah Krakowski: and then… Because of that, it's very difficult in a PDF to really make a sales pitch to somebody.
Jeremiah Krakowski: You want to heavily lean into your follow-up emails, If you do a PDF, Specifically.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And even then, so we tested this out again with my mom's business.
Jeremiah Krakowski: We did, like, 3 or 4 PDF offers. I'll tell you, the amount of sales we got from a PDF offer? Very low.
Jokima: Okay, yeah.
Jeremiah Krakowski: But as soon as we had everybody who signed up for that PDF,
Jeremiah Krakowski: watch a video webinar with Sandy.
Jokima: a ton.
Jeremiah Krakowski: None of those same people then purchased?
Jokima: Yeah.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So it's… so it's like… the commitment level of just a PDF,
Jeremiah Krakowski: To get somebody to sign up?
Jeremiah Krakowski: Very low in terms of persuading, motivating somebody to take action and become a client.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Webinars are still… I would say the most effective medium
Jeremiah Krakowski: For persuading somebody to take action and purchase. The most persuasive medium is actually a phone call.
Jokima: Right, okay.
Jeremiah Krakowski: or a Zoom call, live with the person, sitting down with them one-on-one.
Jokima: Right.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So the most persuasive is if I get you one-on-one on a sales call.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I can really listen individually to what you're going through.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And I can mirror that back to you. And by the way, we actually have a course on that specific topic.
Jokima: Oh, wow, okay.
Jeremiah Krakowski: It's in… is it… let me see where it's at. It is…
Jeremiah Krakowski: See, we have a ton of courses. There's a section that's kind of like a catch-all. I have beginner and intermediate, but then I also have this, learning library of classes right here.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And in the learning library.
Jeremiah Krakowski: There is, like, AI e-book writing, creating courses, like this one, creating a world-class digital course, this one's great. Optimizing your ads, pro video editing, but there's one right here, Mastering Individual Sales.
Jokima: Guide to one-on-one closing.
Jeremiah Krakowski: This is probably one of my favorite courses I ever made.
Jokima: Hmm.
Jeremiah Krakowski: as I go in-depth as far as, like, if you do one-on-one individual sales over the phone or Zoom, how do you lead somebody and persuade them to become a customer?
Jokima: Mmm, okay.
Jeremiah Krakowski: This is, this is, like, the most effective, but it's also the most time-consuming.
Jokima: Right.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So if I'm getting on the phone with somebody to close them as a sale, I can close a lot more sales. Like, for instance, let me tell you, my webinar, my $5 Instagram ads webinar, my… that… and I have people who come in through YouTube, they come in through…
Jeremiah Krakowski: X, they come in through social media, like, I still have people that are coming in off of all those platforms, even when I don't run ads with my evergreen offer.
Jeremiah Krakowski: If my call to action, rather than joining this program, was schedule a call with me, and then I… and then I close people on the phone.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I probably would close a lot more people that way, but the amount of time-consuming.
Jokima: Yeah.
Jeremiah Krakowski: the time-consuming factor would be there. I want to get to where I can have an AI agent
Jeremiah Krakowski: Actually have that conversation through text with somebody.
Jokima: Yeah, yeah.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And we're almost there.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Or the agent could actually do the persuasion based on how I teach, it could study my sales calls and things like that, and learn.
Jokima: how to…
Jeremiah Krakowski: How to do that.
Jeremiah Krakowski: But…
Jokima: Okay.
Jeremiah Krakowski: We're not quite there yet. Anyways…
Jokima: Yeah.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So…
Jokima: Thank you. Bye.
Jeremiah Krakowski: PDF, webinar, sales call. Sales call is time-consuming.
Jokima: Webinar takes some time to set up, but once it's set up, it can sell for you.
Jokima: Yeah.
Jeremiah Krakowski: every time somebody goes to a webinar, I've had 200 people in the last few months go through my webinar.
Jeremiah Krakowski: That's 200 people that got to listen to me for an hour.
Jokima: Yes.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Sell to them, and teach them, and explain everything.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So that's now 200 hours. I cloned myself 200 times.
Jokima: Yeah. Forever.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Every person who sat through the webinar, and they purchased the webinar, too, so they really, they really went through it.
Jokima: Yes.
Jeremiah Krakowski: That's very effective, whereas a PDF, again, a lot of people can read the PDF, a lot of people are gonna skim a PDF,
Jeremiah Krakowski: it's not gonna get deep inside of them to necessarily persuade somebody as much as a webinar would. That's why.
Jokima: webinar.
Jeremiah Krakowski: It's still the most effective way to really persuade people well… cloning yourself.
Jeremiah Krakowski: and not needing yourself to necessarily do that. Now, here's a really cool thing, is with AI,
Jeremiah Krakowski: The tools are getting really fun, where…
Jeremiah Krakowski: You could have the AI actually generate your webinar for you.
Jokima: Mmm. Wow, okay.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I'm creating some tools that can help you with that. There's some different frameworks for that. The AI can actually generate the video for you.
Jeremiah Krakowski: that can do that with an AI avatar tool.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So, like, this is… this is HeyGen right here. This is probably one of the best platforms that's out there that does this.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I… Just playing around with this.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So this is, like, a 6-minute video of me… I wanna fuck you.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And the body language isn't quite there.
Jeremiah Krakowski: The voice inflection isn't quite there.
Jeremiah Krakowski: But it's able to talk, and it's able to communicate.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And then I could… I could intermix B-roll and things like that, and that can be another… that's an emerging, like, effective way to…
Jeremiah Krakowski: do webinars and things like that. You can have the AI write a script for you.
Jeremiah Krakowski: That, that does that.
Jokima: Right.
Jokima: Yeah.
Jokima: Thank you. And just one more thing, I'm just wondering, like, do you… I mean, I know people buy courses for a lot of money.
Jokima: But there's something in my brain that's like, I can't charge anybody more than, like, $197 for, like.
Jokima: You know, like…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Charge… charge 297.
Jokima: Okay.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Go just a little bit above your… comfort zone.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Initially.
Jokima: If you're gonna be running ads, you'll probably need to charge at least $4.97.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Profitable.
Jokima: Oh, wow, okay.
Jokima: Make note, no.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Because you're gonna end up spending about half of that just to get a sale.
Jokima: Oh, okay.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So, like, it's gonna cost you $200 to get that $500 sale.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Okay.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And those ads would go to a $5 offer that then would, like, it might cost you…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Say, $25 per person to get them to sign up for a $5 offer.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Then it might take, like, 8 of those people to get a sale of your $500 course.
Jokima: Okay.
Jeremiah Krakowski: See?
Jokima: Yeah. So 8 times 25 is 200.
Jeremiah Krakowski: You got 8 people that bought a $5 course from you, this is how the math works out. You got 8 people, they bought a $5 course, it cost you $200 in ads to get those 8 people, and 1 or 2 of them purchased your $5 class.
Jeremiah Krakowski: You're still doubling your money, now we can scale that, and that's a… that's a viable business model there.
Jokima: Okay, that makes sense, yeah. I'm just gonna stop being scared and just do 497, because I trust what you're saying, so thank you so much.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Yeah, you bet. You bet.
Jeremiah Krakowski: There is a tool that I, I'm looking to release Possibly…
Jeremiah Krakowski: I'm beta testing how it would look.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Where you guys could actually hire my AI agents to do stuff for you.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And this is something that… so the way that I have it… that it would work is you would submit, kind of, what you would want done by the agents, whether it be scripting your webinar, making a landing page, making a website, making an app, things like that. And then the agent would go in there, and they would start to do the research, and start to do the work for you.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And we could get this stuff going, and then my agents would actually kind of build it for you that way, for a cost, and you would submit it to me to be able to do that.
Jeremiah Krakowski: The way that I structured it was I created, like.
Jeremiah Krakowski: There's sort of an inbox and an outbox, where, like, your request comes into an inbox.
Jeremiah Krakowski: the agent analyzes it, I look at it, I tell the agent how to adjust the plan, and then they output it, they create something, and then send it back to you. And so it might… it would probably need, like, a 48 to 72 hour turnaround.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Per project, but the beauty of it would be
Jeremiah Krakowski: I would be in the mix working through that with you guys, and so… and it would be highly cost-effective, too. It would be… it would not be expensive.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I don't know if you guys would want me to kind of offer a beta of something like that, but…
Jeremiah Krakowski: I'm thinking about offering something like that as a beta test for this group, so…
Jeremiah Krakowski: We'll… we'll look into that, as far as that goes. Nathan, what do you think?
Nathan Fisher: Yeah, I was… I was just gonna say, it would be helpful to have just a list of what, we could do.
Nathan Fisher: Yeah.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Yeah, I would, I would have, I would have them actually…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Brainstorm the higher my agents…
Jeremiah Krakowski: platform for my WCA clients, what could they have it do? Brainstorm this. So, for instance, like, I could just tell my agent to come up with this list right now, and then we could embed that into the app right there. I have a prototype of it, built already.
Jeremiah Krakowski: That we… that we created.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Let me see if I can pull it up here.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And then we'll… and then we're gonna log off after I kind of show you this.
Jeremiah Krakowski: We created… I have this, I have this,
Jeremiah Krakowski: It's called, like, Claude Tools. This is all the different tools that they created for me. These are all the different tools that my agents have created for my business.
Nathan Fisher: No.
Jeremiah Krakowski: And so, let me see, yes, this would be right here… It's not quite ready to… launch yet…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Oh, you know what? That… what's the… dashboard, agent does.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Let me see, I had it… I had it locked down on my app so that people couldn't access them.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Last night, Let me see, some of the core tasks that it could do, it could…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Help you come up with content ideas, sales copy.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Client delivery, research and strategy, ads and analytics, help you come up with ad creatives, landing pages, help you build…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Yeah, there's still some more things to that that I could do, but I'll brainstorm what that might look like.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Okay, here, dashboard, new task, here we go.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Admin…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Let's see, I just have to… Pull this up…
Jeremiah Krakowski: No… Log in… Okay, let me see, once it's logged in, this should work… Okay, dashboard.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So here's this right here, Agent Desk,
Jeremiah Krakowski: It's a dashboard, new tasks, so there's different, like, Tasks that you can do.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Lead magnet creation, custom request, landing page build…
Jeremiah Krakowski: ad copy, email sequence, all those different types of… types of things. We can add more to it. I had it, like.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Okay, create me, an offer. So, like, when you go create a task.
Jeremiah Krakowski: It'll have you submit, okay, what's your offer, who's it for, what's the price point, all of that. And then it'll come to my inbox, and then be able to kind of send it back to you, type of a thing. So this is a very, like, kind of bare-bones, basic app that I had it create.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Or you guys could submit this. It's called Agent Desk. I probably would change the name to it to, like.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Hire my agents type of a thing.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So… Alright.
Nathan Fisher: Alright, what'd be cool is if we could find a way to have these agents go… go find our ideal customer.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Yeah, well…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Going to find the ideal customer, that'd be interesting. So you would just cold message people?
Nathan Fisher: I don't know, I have no idea.
Jeremiah Krakowski: See, the bet… again, the better way to do that is more of the attraction marketing. It can help you create way more, like, viral content, way better ads.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Way better offers that then attract people to you, and then you can start these conversations and have the agents kind of talk to people that way.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Again, that's so much more effective than, like, Spamming people on the internet.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Right, no doubt, no doubt.
Nathan Fisher: Yeah.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So, again, it's the attraction method versus, like, the spamming method, is where the agents can be really helpful. All right, y'all!
Nathan Fisher: Awesome.
Jeremiah Krakowski: This has been a great, kind of, training Q&A. I'm gonna dive deeper into some of this, help bring some of these different trainings and tools to you guys, and we'll talk soon.
Nathan Fisher: Sounds great. Thank you, Jeremiah.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Bye.